id,speaker_nm,conversation_id,reply_to_nm,timestamp,text,likes,shares,num_comments,cleaned_text,named_entities,sentiment,tokens
1339230232088367105,MrAndyNgo,1339230232088367105,None,2020-12-16 15:25:43,"BLM-antifa in Seattle have set up another autonomous zone at Cal Anderson Park in the Capital Hill neighborhood. This is the same area they made CHAZ during the summer months. Video by 
@choeshow
:",5200,2700,1400,blmantifa seattle set autonomous zone cal anderson park capital hill neighborhood area chaz summer months video choeshow,"[('BLM-antifa', 'ORG'), ('Seattle', 'GPE'), ('Cal Anderson Park', 'FAC'), ('Capital Hill', 'LOC'), ('the summer months', 'DATE')]",0.2,"[101, 1038, 12624, 3775, 7011, 5862, 2275, 8392, 4224, 10250, 5143, 2380, 3007, 2940, 5101, 2181, 15775, 2480, 2621, 2706, 2678, 16480, 9953, 5004, 102]"
1339230948488073219,Freakoutery,1339230232088367105,MrAndyNgo,2020-12-16 15:28:34,"At some point it seems as if we could just start tweeting out videos of landfills and Haitian ghettos and say ""another autonomous zone has erupted in ___"" and they'd be totally believable.",113,2,1,point just start tweeting videos landfills haitian ghettos say autonomous zone erupted theyd totally believable,"[('Haitian', 'NORP')]",0.45,"[101, 2391, 2074, 2707, 1056, 28394, 3436, 6876, 28382, 2015, 21404, 17276, 2015, 2360, 8392, 4224, 12591, 2027, 2094, 6135, 19337, 2666, 12423, 102]"
1339451172659322882,DevinCow,1339230232088367105,MrAndyNgo,2020-12-17 06:03:40,"Hay 
@KathrynTewson
 they’re lying again",13,0,1,hay kathryntewson theyre lying,[],0.0,"[101, 10974, 20484, 2618, 9333, 2239, 2027, 2890, 4688, 102]"
1339236439620349957,palindromemood,1339230232088367105,MrAndyNgo,2020-12-16 15:50:23,"This is what we have to look forward to in the Harris/Biden administration. By the time the sympathizers wake up, it’ll be too late.",87,5,2,look forward harrisbiden administration time sympathizers wake itll late,"[('Biden', 'PERSON')]",-0.3,"[101, 2298, 2830, 5671, 17062, 2368, 3447, 2051, 25353, 8737, 25457, 16750, 5256, 2009, 3363, 2397, 102]"
1339231536642629632,kmcannistraci,1339230232088367105,MrAndyNgo,2020-12-16 15:30:54,1 time my kid put a note on the door”don’t come in”. I took the door off for a year. That what you do when children throw tantrums. Also you would think with all those collective people together they could come up with a system to clean that place up. Come on man!,74,3,10,1 time kid note doordont come took door year children throw tantrums think collective people come clean place come man,"[('1', 'CARDINAL'), ('a year', 'DATE')]",0.45833333333333337,"[101, 1015, 2051, 4845, 3602, 2341, 5280, 2102, 2272, 2165, 2341, 2095, 2336, 5466, 9092, 24456, 2015, 2228, 7268, 2111, 2272, 4550, 2173, 2272, 2158, 102]"
1339231959927631873,skol_brian,1339230232088367105,MrAndyNgo,2020-12-16 15:32:35,Andy cuts the video and calls it a CHAZ when it's a homeless encampment.  Not surprising. Gotta get those Ngo Simps fird up right?,50,1,34,andy cuts video calls chaz homeless encampment surprising gotta ngo simps fird right,"[('Andy', 'PERSON'), ('Ngo Simps', 'GPE')]",-0.03214285714285714,"[101, 5557, 7659, 2678, 4455, 15775, 2480, 11573, 4372, 26468, 3672, 11341, 10657, 17895, 21934, 4523, 21554, 2094, 2157, 102]"
1339234000162844674,St3veOlson,1339230232088367105,MrAndyNgo,2020-12-16 15:40:42,"I totally support this. As long as we get to build an additional wall around them and never let them come out. Once their supplies diminish, it would only be a matter of time before the problem would resolve itself.",14,0,1,totally support long build additional wall let come supplies diminish matter time problem resolve,[],-0.016666666666666666,"[101, 6135, 2490, 2146, 3857, 3176, 2813, 2292, 2272, 6067, 11737, 5498, 4095, 3043, 2051, 3291, 10663, 102]"
1339313377177460743,ShraderKs,1339230232088367105,MrAndyNgo,2020-12-16 20:56:07,Wait antifa is a myth! BLM is a multi-billion dollar organization they wouldn't live like this!! Would they? This is what the left has given birth too. How in the world did 81 million people vote for this?,10,1,8,wait antifa myth blm multibillion dollar organization wouldnt live like left given birth world did 81 million people vote,"[('BLM', 'ORG'), ('multi-billion dollar', 'MONEY'), ('81 million', 'CARDINAL')]",0.1065340909090909,"[101, 3524, 3424, 7011, 10661, 1038, 13728, 4800, 24457, 3258, 7922, 3029, 2876, 2102, 2444, 2066, 2187, 2445, 4182, 2088, 2106, 6282, 2454, 2111, 3789, 102]"
1339231336867966980,wilconorth_j,1339230232088367105,MrAndyNgo,2020-12-16 15:30:07,It’s really wonderful what they’ve been able to build,9,0,1,really wonderful theyve able build,[],0.75,"[101, 2428, 6919, 2027, 3726, 2583, 3857, 102]"
1339342589951176718,Designsage,1339230232088367105,MrAndyNgo,2020-12-16 22:52:11,"Wow, Seattle is starting to look like a third world country. WOW.",5,1,1,wow seattle starting look like world country wow,"[('Seattle', 'GPE'), ('WOW', 'ORG')]",0.05,"[101, 10166, 5862, 3225, 2298, 2066, 2088, 2406, 10166, 102]"
1339345626119671809,OlCurt66,1339230232088367105,MrAndyNgo,2020-12-16 23:04:15,"I’ve said it before and will again. I have no more sympathy for the folks living there. If they won’t band together to stop this, so be it.",7,0,3,ive said sympathy folks living wont band stop,[],-0.25,"[101, 4921, 2063, 2056, 11883, 12455, 2542, 2180, 2102, 2316, 2644, 102]"
1339232994905743360,EdwinHoward1144,1339230232088367105,MrAndyNgo,2020-12-16 15:36:42,"Keep the faith, Trump’s hellfire is about to rain down on the anarcho-communists and the deep state.",4,1,2,faith trumps hellfire rain anarchocommunists deep state,"[('Trump', 'ORG')]",-0.07777777777777779,"[101, 4752, 8398, 2015, 3109, 10273, 4542, 9617, 11140, 24163, 7382, 19496, 12837, 2784, 2110, 102]"
1337813537482223618,thehill,1337813537482223618,None,2020-12-12 17:36:17,"WATCH: Trump supporters gather in Washington, D.C. on Saturday.",589,302,441,watch trump supporters gather washington dc saturday,"[('Washington', 'GPE'), ('D.C.', 'GPE'), ('Saturday', 'DATE')]",0.0,"[101, 3422, 8398, 6793, 8587, 2899, 5887, 5095, 102]"
1337814925301919744,wireframejames,1337813537482223618,thehill,2020-12-12 17:41:48,Imagine if women turned out in support of Trump? It might look like this.,30,6,0,imagine women turned support trump look like,"[('Trump', 'ORG')]",0.0,"[101, 5674, 2308, 2357, 2490, 8398, 2298, 2066, 102]"
1337813689378861056,chin_dogg,1337813537482223618,thehill,2020-12-12 17:36:53,Is this Egypt? Cause that looks like a river of denial,48,0,6,egypt cause looks like river denial,"[('Egypt', 'GPE')]",0.0,"[101, 5279, 3426, 3504, 2066, 2314, 14920, 102]"
1337818431907880961,JGaffneyUSN,1337813537482223618,thehill,2020-12-12 17:55:44,How did they scrape up the gas money?,25,1,0,did scrape gas money,[],0.0,"[101, 2106, 26988, 3806, 2769, 102]"
1337813722144837632,ElyseBurden,1337813537482223618,thehill,2020-12-12 17:37:01,Who cares what they do,26,0,1,cares,[],0.0,"[101, 14977, 102]"
1337815027437473794,BeingJWood,1337813537482223618,thehill,2020-12-12 17:42:12,Maybe more of them should have voted in the election. It’s tough to carry a candidate with approval in the low 40’s over the finish line.,12,1,2,maybe voted election tough carry candidate approval low 40s finish line,"[('40', 'CARDINAL')]",0.037037037037037035,"[101, 2672, 5444, 2602, 7823, 4287, 4018, 6226, 2659, 2871, 2015, 3926, 2240, 102]"
1337814119072886784,ezautoleasesale,1337813537482223618,thehill,2020-12-12 17:38:36,"If Trump was the patriot he claims to be, he would quash this foolishness, admit he has lost fair and square, concede the election and tell his sycophants to go home.   Election is over, but oh now....he cant do that.",12,0,5,trump patriot claims quash foolishness admit lost fair square concede election tell sycophants home election oh nowhe,"[('Trump', 'PERSON')]",0.7,"[101, 8398, 16419, 4447, 24209, 11823, 13219, 2791, 6449, 2439, 4189, 2675, 9530, 22119, 2602, 2425, 25353, 3597, 21890, 7666, 2188, 2602, 2821, 2085, 5369, 102]"
1337814154921431040,PaulStaebell,1337813537482223618,thehill,2020-12-12 17:38:44,WOW That crowd is almost as big as his Inaugeration,12,0,0,wow crowd big inaugeration,"[('WOW', 'ORG'), ('Inaugeration', 'FAC')]",0.05,"[101, 10166, 4306, 2502, 27118, 22890, 8156, 102]"
1337816652361199618,DrJones03046447,1337813537482223618,thehill,2020-12-12 17:48:40,How come he had 71 million votes and can only get a crowd of around a thousand like this in Washington? Something fishy - this shows the true cult of Trump ... which really is pretty small!,8,2,0,come 71 million votes crowd thousand like washington fishy shows true cult trump really pretty small,"[('71 million', 'CARDINAL'), ('around a thousand', 'CARDINAL'), ('Washington', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]",0.071875,"[101, 2272, 6390, 2454, 4494, 4306, 4595, 2066, 2899, 3869, 2100, 3065, 2995, 8754, 8398, 2428, 3492, 2235, 102]"
1337813634639155201,GodSavesToday,1337813537482223618,thehill,2020-12-12 17:36:40,"Am I the only one hoping to watch the Secret Service carry that Orange Clown out on January 20th? 
#ITSOVER",10,0,2,hoping watch secret service carry orange clown january 20th itsover,"[('the Secret Service', 'ORG'), ('Orange Clown', 'LOC'), ('January 20th', 'DATE'), ('ITSOVER', 'PERSON')]",-0.13333333333333333,"[101, 5327, 3422, 3595, 2326, 4287, 4589, 15912, 2254, 3983, 2049, 7840, 102]"
1345179662880624641,choeshow,1345179662880624641,None,2021-01-02 01:26:38,"NEW YEAR’S EVE DESTRUCTION: Capitol Hill biz owners and neighbors are fed up with black bloc marchers wrecking the city. The owner of Cafe Argento says they’re being targeted for just trying to improve the neighborhood.

Story 6pm 
@komonews
 

#seattle #CalAndersonPark",271,112,56,new years eve destruction capitol hill biz owners neighbors fed black bloc marchers wrecking city owner cafe argento says theyre targeted just trying improve neighborhood story 6pm komonews seattle calandersonpark,"[('Capitol Hill', 'ORG'), ('Cafe Argento', 'ORG'), ('6pm', 'TIME'), ('#', 'CARDINAL')]",-0.015151515151515152,"[101, 2047, 2086, 6574, 6215, 9424, 2940, 12170, 2480, 5608, 10638, 7349, 2304, 15984, 28791, 2869, 12006, 2075, 2103, 3954, 7668, 23157, 2080, 2758, 2027, 2890, 9416, 2074, 2667, 5335, 5101, 2466, 1020, 9737, 12849, 8202, 7974, 2015, 5862, 10250, 12243, 3385, 14432, 102]"
1345186143931797505,flottum76lynn,1345179662880624641,choeshow,2021-01-02 01:52:23,"Well, when you catch and release these idiots night after night, this is what happens. Maybe try voting next time for a candidate without a “D” next to their name. This will never end.",68,3,4,catch release idiots night night happens maybe try voting time candidate d end,"[('night', 'TIME')]",-0.26666666666666666,"[101, 4608, 2713, 28781, 2305, 2305, 6433, 2672, 3046, 6830, 2051, 4018, 1040, 2203, 102]"
1345182726584844290,integrityiseve1,1345179662880624641,choeshow,2021-01-02 01:38:48,Why bother trying to improve the neighborhood. Open in a place that will appreciate your efforts,43,0,1,bother trying improve neighborhood open place appreciate efforts,[],0.0,"[101, 8572, 2667, 5335, 5101, 2330, 2173, 9120, 4073, 102]"
1345180938653732870,ScreamingInSea,1345179662880624641,choeshow,2021-01-02 01:31:42,"Smashing up another LGBT POC owned small business. 

It feels like the gay bars/clubs/even coffee shops are targeted more then anyone else. 
Look what happened to QueerBar & Neighbors.",14,0,2,smashing lgbt poc owned small business feels like gay barsclubseven coffee shops targeted look happened queerbar neighbors,"[('LGBT POC', 'ORG'), ('QueerBar & Neighbors', 'ORG')]",0.22222222222222224,"[101, 21105, 12010, 13433, 2278, 3079, 2235, 2449, 5683, 2066, 5637, 6963, 20464, 12083, 3366, 8159, 4157, 7340, 9416, 2298, 3047, 19483, 8237, 10638, 102]"
1345181731200983041,RBtw33ts,1345179662880624641,choeshow,2021-01-02 01:34:51,It is never ok to destroy someone else’s property.  If you do not like a business don’t go there.,9,0,0,ok destroy elses property like business dont,[],-0.225,"[101, 7929, 6033, 2842, 2015, 3200, 2066, 2449, 2123, 2102, 102]"
1345195592004194305,Chrismorama,1345179662880624641,choeshow,2021-01-02 02:29:56,The coming backlash will be severe.,9,0,1,coming backlash severe,[],0.0,"[101, 2746, 25748, 5729, 102]"
1345235076913782784,cwgrl42632,1345179662880624641,choeshow,2021-01-02 05:06:50,You should ask all these fed up residents and business owners who they have been voting for over the last 10-15 years....,9,0,1,ask fed residents business owners voting 1015 years,"[('the last', 'DATE'), ('10-15 years', 'DATE')]",0.0,"[101, 3198, 7349, 3901, 2449, 5608, 6830, 7886, 2629, 2086, 102]"
1345211225475571713,LoneStarWhiz,1345179662880624641,choeshow,2021-01-02 03:32:03,You voted them into power.,4,0,0,voted power,[],0.0,"[101, 5444, 2373, 102]"
1345185595891404800,mchellshit,1345179662880624641,choeshow,2021-01-02 01:50:13,"Congrats, Jeff Bezos is now that much richer.",3,0,0,congrats jeff bezos richer,"[('Congrats', 'NORP'), ('Jeff Bezos', 'PERSON')]",0.2,"[101, 26478, 8609, 2015, 5076, 2022, 28370, 26108, 102]"
1345401572898050050,lynstar_16,1345179662880624641,choeshow,2021-01-02 16:08:25,These people are so destructive. If they could only put their energy into something positive and constructive.,3,0,0,people destructive energy positive constructive,[],-0.12424242424242422,"[101, 2111, 15615, 2943, 3893, 26157, 102]"
1345182925621317639,TheDigriz,1345179662880624641,choeshow,2021-01-02 01:39:36,Time for him to buy a gun.,2,0,0,time buy gun,[],0.0,"[101, 2051, 4965, 3282, 102]"
1345201642224943105,MikeHalston2,1345179662880624641,choeshow,2021-01-02 02:53:58,"Too bad.
Why don't they ask their stupid fellow citizens to stop voting for far-left appeasers of this cancerous ideology?
And if their fellow citizens aren't interested in safety, amenity, economic prosperity etc. then get the hell out of these rotten far-left hellholes!",1,0,0,bad dont ask stupid fellow citizens stop voting farleft appeasers cancerous ideology fellow citizens arent interested safety amenity economic prosperity hell rotten farleft hellholes,[],-0.24999999999999994,"[101, 2919, 2123, 2102, 3198, 5236, 3507, 4480, 2644, 6830, 2521, 2571, 6199, 10439, 19500, 2869, 4456, 3560, 13165, 3507, 4480, 4995, 2102, 4699, 3808, 2572, 20693, 3171, 14165, 3109, 11083, 2521, 2571, 6199, 3109, 19990, 102]"
1339624669750681600,MayorBowser,1339624669750681600,None,2020-12-17 17:33:04,"Today, our frontline workers received their first dose of the COVID-19 vaccine at Kaiser Permanente in Capitol Hill. These vaccinations will save lives & protect our first responders, their patients, and their families. 

There is reason to have hope. 

#GetVaccinatedDC, #DCHOPE",154,38,10,today frontline workers received dose covid19 vaccine kaiser permanente capitol hill vaccinations save lives protect responders patients families reason hope getvaccinateddc dchope,"[('Today', 'DATE'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('COVID-19', 'ORG'), ('Kaiser Permanente', 'FAC'), ('Capitol Hill', 'ORG'), ('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('DCHOPE', 'PERSON')]",0.25,"[101, 2651, 2392, 4179, 3667, 2363, 13004, 2522, 17258, 16147, 17404, 15676, 4568, 2063, 9424, 2940, 12436, 14693, 9323, 2015, 3828, 3268, 4047, 6869, 2545, 5022, 2945, 3114, 3246, 2131, 24887, 28748, 3064, 16409, 5887, 26441, 102]"
1341245162442375168,ShorePoint888,1339624669750681600,MayorBowser,2020-12-22 04:52:20,"Why is the Director of Health, Dr. LaQuandra Nesbitt, always so  unhappy?",1,0,0,director health dr laquandra nesbitt unhappy,"[('LaQuandra Nesbitt', 'PERSON')]",-0.6,"[101, 2472, 2740, 2852, 2474, 16211, 17670, 24524, 16313, 2102, 12511, 102]"
1339677807740383234,2DeCee,1339624669750681600,MayorBowser,2020-12-17 21:04:14,Thank you for the update Madam Mayor,0,0,1,thank update madam mayor,"[('Madam', 'PERSON')]",0.0,"[101, 4067, 10651, 21658, 3664, 102]"
1346148068773789697,CBSEveningNews,1346148068773789697,None,2021-01-04 17:34:44,"At least a dozen GOP senators are vowing to challenge President-elect Joe Biden’s election victory on Wednesday.

Some have cited baseless conspiracy theories about the election as disputes over the results split the Republican party on Capitol Hill.",4,6,6,dozen gop senators vowing challenge presidentelect joe bidens election victory wednesday cited baseless conspiracy theories election disputes results split republican party capitol hill,"[('At least a dozen', 'CARDINAL'), ('GOP', 'ORG'), ('Joe Biden’s', 'PERSON'), ('Wednesday', 'DATE'), ('the Republican party', 'ORG'), ('Capitol Hill', 'ORG')]",-0.3,"[101, 6474, 2175, 2361, 10153, 19076, 2075, 4119, 2343, 12260, 6593, 3533, 7226, 6132, 2602, 3377, 9317, 6563, 14040, 7971, 9714, 8106, 2602, 11936, 3463, 3975, 3951, 2283, 9424, 2940, 102]"
1346148970440118274,airwest007,1346148068773789697,CBSEveningNews,2021-01-04 17:38:19,cBSnews  M$M,1,0,0,cbsnews mm,[],0.0,"[101, 6568, 2638, 9333, 3461, 102]"
1346183164989992960,tompach09234046,1346148068773789697,CBSEveningNews,2021-01-04 19:54:12,Is this the seditious twelve ,1,0,0,seditious,"[('twelve', 'CARDINAL')]",0.0,"[101, 7367, 23194, 6313, 102]"
1346150649780719617,CapsHockey1974,1346148068773789697,CBSEveningNews,2021-01-04 17:44:59,"They know that it won’t go anywhere, but their objections are going to be rejected by the Senate when it comes to a vote. It’s about their future political ambitions.",0,0,0,know wont objections going rejected senate comes vote future political ambitions,"[('Senate', 'ORG')]",0.0,"[101, 2113, 2180, 2102, 17304, 2183, 5837, 4001, 3310, 3789, 2925, 2576, 19509, 102]"
1346153959619231746,choytdad,1346148068773789697,CBSEveningNews,2021-01-04 17:58:08,"Why describe it as “baseless conspiracy theories” when there is video evidence showing suitcases of ballots being drawn under a covered table after the Republican poll watchers were told to go home.
These tens of thousands of ballots were then processed between 10.35 pm and1.00am",0,0,0,baseless conspiracy theories video evidence showing suitcases ballots drawn covered table republican poll watchers told home tens thousands ballots processed 1035 pm and100am,"[('Republican', 'NORP'), ('These tens of thousands', 'CARDINAL'), ('10.35 pm', 'TIME')]",0.0,"[101, 14040, 7971, 9714, 8106, 2678, 3350, 4760, 15940, 2015, 17069, 4567, 3139, 2795, 3951, 8554, 3422, 2545, 2409, 2188, 15295, 5190, 17069, 13995, 9800, 2629, 7610, 1998, 18613, 3286, 102]"
1335507416331390976,KatieDaviscourt,1335507416331390976,None,2020-12-06 08:52:35,"OLYMPIA, WA: Shots were fired earlier today outside of the Washington State Capitol during a clash between Antifa Militants and Patriots. The Olympia Police Department has the man in custody and is investigating.

*Warning*—Video Via BL Ranch on YT",211,84,27,olympia wa shots fired earlier today outside washington state capitol clash antifa militants patriots olympia police department man custody investigating warningvideo bl ranch yt,"[('earlier today', 'TIME'), ('Washington State', 'GPE'), ('Capitol', 'ORG'), ('Antifa Militants', 'ORG'), ('Patriots', 'ORG'), ('The Olympia Police Department', 'ORG'), ('YT', 'GPE')]",0.0,"[101, 17096, 11333, 7171, 5045, 3041, 2651, 2648, 2899, 2110, 9424, 13249, 3424, 7011, 17671, 11579, 17096, 2610, 2533, 2158, 9968, 11538, 5432, 17258, 8780, 1038, 2140, 8086, 1061, 2102, 102]"
1335507418411745283,KatieDaviscourt,1335507416331390976,KatieDaviscourt,2020-12-06 08:52:35,"Statement from 
@OlyPD
:",34,7,4,statement olypd,[],0.0,"[101, 4861, 19330, 22571, 2094, 102]"
1338299732918063105,GunWashington,1335507416331390976,KatieDaviscourt,2020-12-14 01:48:15,"If anyone actually saw this incident in Olympia this weekend, please contact Washington Gun Law today at 425.765.0487 immediately.",0,0,0,actually saw incident olympia weekend contact washington gun law today 4257650487 immediately,"[('Olympia', 'GPE'), ('this weekend', 'DATE'), ('Washington Gun Law', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('today', 'DATE')]",0.0,"[101, 2941, 2387, 5043, 17096, 5353, 3967, 2899, 3282, 2375, 2651, 23285, 2581, 26187, 2692, 18139, 2581, 3202, 102]"
1335749559448973316,ColleenAnderso2,1335507416331390976,KatieDaviscourt,2020-12-07 00:54:46,https://facebook.com/112779115408517/posts/4108502765836112/?d=n…. It was trump follower who was arrested. So much for “law and order”.,7,0,3,trump follower arrested law order,[],0.2,"[101, 8398, 22399, 4727, 2375, 2344, 102]"
1335564467149524992,WRB_BOB,1335507416331390976,KatieDaviscourt,2020-12-06 12:39:17,Looks like the guy in the bright yellow was defending him self this video I hope help him,5,0,2,looks like guy bright yellow defending self video hope help,[],0.35000000000000003,"[101, 3504, 2066, 3124, 4408, 3756, 6984, 2969, 2678, 3246, 2393, 102]"
1335598262099746818,Hydro_Sparky,1335507416331390976,KatieDaviscourt,2020-12-06 14:53:34,"Oly PD doing the typical, ignore attacks by the violent left and arrest their victims who defend themselves, routine.

I refuse to believe this is the will of the people. We need voter ID reform so elected officials have to care about the average citizen again",5,0,1,oly pd doing typical ignore attacks violent left arrest victims defend routine refuse believe people need voter id reform elected officials care average citizen,"[('Oly PD', 'ORG')]",-0.2333333333333333,"[101, 19330, 2100, 22851, 2725, 5171, 8568, 4491, 6355, 2187, 6545, 5694, 6985, 9410, 10214, 2903, 2111, 2342, 14303, 8909, 5290, 2700, 4584, 2729, 2779, 6926, 102]"
1337930542348718083,MegMadison13,1335507416331390976,KatieDaviscourt,2020-12-13 01:21:13,There is no such thing as an Antifa militant! Do you actually know what Antifa means??? Idiot!,3,0,0,thing antifa militant actually know antifa means idiot,"[('Antifa', 'NORP'), ('Antifa', 'ORG'), ('Idiot', 'PERSON')]",-0.3333333333333333,"[101, 2518, 3424, 7011, 16830, 2941, 2113, 3424, 7011, 2965, 10041, 102]"
1336086725458726912,AmazonFortress,1335507416331390976,KatieDaviscourt,2020-12-07 23:14:33,Antifa would always show up to Patriots peaceful rallies to start trouble.,1,0,0,antifa patriots peaceful rallies start trouble,"[('Antifa', 'ORG'), ('Patriots', 'ORG')]",0.024999999999999994,"[101, 3424, 7011, 11579, 9379, 22867, 2707, 4390, 102]"
1337923429308100608,hummingbirddab,1335507416331390976,KatieDaviscourt,2020-12-13 00:52:57,Just say trump supporter shot multiple times at anti trump supporters..and was hogtied and carried off. Hope he rots!!,1,0,0,just say trump supporter shot multiple times anti trump supportersand hogtied carried hope rots,[],0.0,"[101, 2074, 2360, 8398, 10129, 2915, 3674, 2335, 3424, 8398, 6793, 5685, 27589, 9515, 2094, 3344, 3246, 18672, 2015, 102]"
1337929123918979074,KevinKennedy002,1335507416331390976,KatieDaviscourt,2020-12-13 01:15:35,Stop those criminal white supremacy gangs. Those proud boys need to stop their violence.,1,0,0,stop criminal white supremacy gangs proud boys need stop violence,[],0.13333333333333333,"[101, 2644, 4735, 2317, 22006, 18542, 7098, 3337, 2342, 2644, 4808, 102]"
1337929493420380161,phoenixmacleod1,1335507416331390976,KatieDaviscourt,2020-12-13 01:17:03,lol you aren’t a reporter. You are a joke. The labels you have chosen show that you aren’t a real reporter.,1,0,0,lol arent reporter joke labels chosen arent real reporter,[],0.5,"[101, 8840, 2140, 4995, 2102, 6398, 8257, 10873, 4217, 4995, 2102, 2613, 6398, 102]"
1346193314727518211,MonoNeon,1346193314727518211,None,2021-01-04 20:34:31,"NEW ALBUM OUT NOW
“Banana Peel On Capitol Hill”
LINK: https://dywanethomasjr.bandcamp.com/album/banana-peel-on-capitol-hill…

“Yesterday the world was buried alive”

Stanks ya for listening to whateva the fyuck I be doing... ",22,8,0,new album banana peel capitol hill link yesterday world buried alive stanks ya listening whateva fyuck doing,"[('Banana Peel On Capitol Hill', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('Yesterday', 'DATE')]",0.11818181818181818,"[101, 2047, 2201, 15212, 14113, 9424, 2940, 4957, 7483, 2088, 3950, 4142, 9761, 5705, 8038, 5962, 2054, 13331, 1042, 10513, 3600, 2725, 102]"
1337770272963825665,FordFischer,1337770272963825665,None,2020-12-12 14:44:22,"Worth noting that because there’s a few separate rally points (I misspelled this as “tally” in my first tweet of this thread, sorry) some people are already marching east toward the Capitol / rally point on national mall from Freedom Plaza.",119,18,8,worth noting theres separate rally points misspelled tally tweet thread sorry people marching east capitol rally point national mall freedom plaza,"[('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Capitol', 'ORG'), ('Freedom Plaza', 'LOC')]",-0.037500000000000006,"[101, 4276, 9073, 2045, 2015, 3584, 8320, 2685, 3335, 11880, 3709, 19552, 1056, 28394, 2102, 11689, 3374, 2111, 10998, 2264, 9424, 8320, 2391, 2120, 6670, 4071, 8232, 102]"
1337769536674820101,FordFischer,1337770272963825665,FordFischer,2020-12-12 14:41:26,"The “Trump Unity Bridge” is parked right now and playing “God Bless America” at 11th and Penn, between Harry’s Bar and the Trump hotel.",98,31,13,trump unity bridge parked right playing god bless america 11th penn harrys bar trump hotel,"[('Trump Unity Bridge', 'WORK_OF_ART'), ('11th', 'ORDINAL'), ('Penn', 'PERSON'), ('Harry’s Bar', 'PERSON'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]",0.2857142857142857,"[101, 8398, 8499, 2958, 9083, 2157, 2652, 2643, 19994, 2637, 6252, 9502, 4302, 2015, 3347, 8398, 3309, 102]"
1337770272963825665,FordFischer,1337770272963825665,FordFischer,2020-12-12 14:44:22,"Worth noting that because there’s a few separate rally points (I misspelled this as “tally” in my first tweet of this thread, sorry) some people are already marching east toward the Capitol / rally point on national mall from Freedom Plaza.",119,18,8,worth noting theres separate rally points misspelled tally tweet thread sorry people marching east capitol rally point national mall freedom plaza,"[('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('Capitol', 'ORG'), ('Freedom Plaza', 'LOC')]",-0.037500000000000006,"[101, 4276, 9073, 2045, 2015, 3584, 8320, 2685, 3335, 11880, 3709, 19552, 1056, 28394, 2102, 11689, 3374, 2111, 10998, 2264, 9424, 8320, 2391, 2120, 6670, 4071, 8232, 102]"
1337775819918348288,FordFischer,1337770272963825665,FordFischer,2020-12-12 15:06:24,"Chants of “Fuck antifa!”

Livestreaming momentarily.",153,27,19,chants fuck antifa livestreaming momentarily,[],-0.5,"[101, 29534, 6616, 3424, 7011, 3268, 25379, 2075, 16032, 102]"
1337801700619522049,FordFischer,1337770272963825665,FordFischer,2020-12-12 16:49:15,I livestreamed for about an hour before connection died due to too many people.,97,7,10,livestreamed hour connection died people,"[('about an hour', 'TIME')]",0.1875,"[101, 3268, 25379, 2098, 3178, 4434, 2351, 2111, 102]"
1337812463132217346,FordFischer,1337770272963825665,FordFischer,2020-12-12 17:32:01,"Trump supporters wave as Marine One flies overhead, presumably carrying the president.",158,41,22,trump supporters wave marine flies overhead presumably carrying president,"[('Marine One', 'ORG')]",0.0,"[101, 8398, 6793, 4400, 3884, 10029, 8964, 10712, 4755, 2343, 102]"
1337813883407446021,FordFischer,1337770272963825665,FordFischer,2020-12-12 17:37:39,"Something challenging out here is they there’s multiple different rallies. Several blocks away from the March for Trump based at Freedom Plaza is the “Jericho March”, framed as a prayer rally for Trump. Apparently General Flynn just spoke here.",151,45,17,challenging theres multiple different rallies blocks away march trump based freedom plaza jericho march framed prayer rally trump apparently general flynn just spoke,"[('March', 'DATE'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Freedom Plaza', 'FAC'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Flynn', 'PERSON')]",0.11000000000000001,"[101, 10368, 2045, 2015, 3674, 2367, 22867, 5991, 2185, 2233, 8398, 2241, 4071, 8232, 17309, 2233, 10366, 7083, 8320, 8398, 4593, 2236, 13259, 2074, 3764, 102]"
1337826194209828865,FordFischer,1337770272963825665,FordFischer,2020-12-12 18:26:34,"At the #JerichoMarch, Stop the Steal founder 
@ali
 lays out that their last hope after the electoral college is that a senator will join Rep. Mo Brooks in blocking Jan 6 certification of Biden win.

If none do, “we will burn the Republican Party down and make something new.”",225,137,46,jerichomarch stop steal founder ali lays hope electoral college senator join rep mo brooks blocking jan 6 certification biden win burn republican party make new,"[('JerichoMarch', 'PERSON'), ('Steal', 'ORG'), ('Mo Brooks', 'PERSON'), ('Jan 6', 'DATE'), ('Biden', 'PERSON'), ('the Republican Party', 'ORG')]",0.1952020202020202,"[101, 17309, 7849, 2818, 2644, 8954, 3910, 4862, 19764, 3246, 6092, 2267, 5205, 3693, 16360, 9587, 8379, 10851, 5553, 1020, 10618, 7226, 2368, 2663, 6402, 3951, 2283, 2191, 2047, 102]"
1337827287161589761,FordFischer,1337770272963825665,FordFischer,2020-12-12 18:30:55,"Alex Jones also spoke, promising that “we will never recognize” Joe Biden.

Cheers erupted when he declared that “Joe Biden is a globalist, and Joe Biden will be removed one way or another.”",203,157,58,alex jones spoke promising recognize joe biden cheers erupted declared joe biden globalist joe biden removed way,"[('Alex Jones', 'PERSON'), ('Joe Biden', 'PERSON'), ('Joe Biden', 'PERSON'), ('Joe Biden', 'PERSON'), ('one', 'CARDINAL')]",0.2,"[101, 4074, 3557, 3764, 10015, 6807, 3533, 7226, 2368, 21250, 12591, 4161, 3533, 7226, 2368, 3795, 2923, 3533, 7226, 2368, 3718, 2126, 102]"
1337836729542336515,FordFischer,1337770272963825665,FordFischer,2020-12-12 19:08:26,General Flynn just spoke as well at Freedom Plaza. He leaves encouraging Trump supporters not to give up and instead “fight like a Flynn!”,146,58,53,general flynn just spoke freedom plaza leaves encouraging trump supporters instead fight like flynn,"[('Flynn', 'PERSON'), ('Freedom Plaza', 'FAC'), ('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Flynn', 'PERSON')]",0.06250000000000003,"[101, 2236, 13259, 2074, 3764, 4071, 8232, 3727, 11434, 8398, 6793, 2612, 2954, 2066, 13259, 102]"
1346153540763459584,AreaFada1,1346153540763459584,None,2021-01-04 17:56:29,Astonishing new evidence of a desperate President Donald Dickhead Trump caught on tape trying to steal the election exposes the depth of his corruption and makes his Republican Capitol Hill allies complicit in his bid to thwart the will of voters.,4,2,2,astonishing new evidence desperate president donald dickhead trump caught tape trying steal election exposes depth corruption makes republican capitol hill allies complicit bid thwart voters,"[('Donald Dickhead Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Republican', 'NORP'), ('Capitol Hill', 'ORG')]",0.012121212121212125,"[101, 26137, 2047, 3350, 7143, 2343, 6221, 5980, 4974, 8398, 3236, 6823, 2667, 8954, 2602, 14451, 2015, 5995, 7897, 3084, 3951, 9424, 2940, 6956, 4012, 24759, 28775, 2102, 7226, 16215, 18367, 7206, 102]"
1346153544886358021,AreaFada1,1346153540763459584,AreaFada1,2021-01-04 17:56:30,"In a fresh abuse of power, Trump tried to bully a top Georgia GOP official into finding votes to overturn President-elect Joe Biden's win in the state. The staggering telephone call, audio of which was obtained by the Washington Post, amounted to the most serious threat yet.",0,0,1,fresh abuse power trump tried bully georgia gop official finding votes overturn presidentelect joe bidens win state staggering telephone audio obtained washington post amounted threat,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Georgia', 'GPE'), ('GOP', 'ORG'), (""Joe Biden's"", 'PERSON'), ('the Washington Post', 'ORG')]",0.3533333333333334,"[101, 4840, 6905, 2373, 8398, 2699, 20716, 4108, 2175, 2361, 2880, 4531, 4494, 2058, 22299, 2343, 12260, 6593, 3533, 7226, 6132, 2663, 2110, 26233, 7026, 5746, 4663, 2899, 2695, 18779, 5081, 102]"
1346154955846070272,asktja,1346153540763459584,AreaFada1,2021-01-04 18:02:06,And UN is watching without any warning,1,0,0,watching warning,"[('UN', 'ORG')]",0.0,"[101, 3666, 5432, 102]"
1346093123353649153,wolfblitzer,1346093123353649153,None,2021-01-04 13:56:24,"I drove by Capitol Hill this morning to see the construction underway for the Inauguration. The crowd will be very limited because of the deadly coronavirus pandemic. Sixteen days until 
@JoeBiden
 becomes President.",1800,141,83,drove capitol hill morning construction underway inauguration crowd limited deadly coronavirus pandemic sixteen days joebiden president,"[('Capitol Hill', 'ORG'), ('this morning', 'TIME'), ('Inauguration', 'ORG'), ('Sixteen days', 'DATE')]",-0.14642857142857144,"[101, 5225, 9424, 2940, 2851, 2810, 14128, 17331, 4306, 3132, 9252, 21887, 23350, 6090, 3207, 7712, 7032, 2420, 3533, 17062, 2368, 2343, 102]"
1346093420490723328,azuna_eth,1346093123353649153,wolfblitzer,2021-01-04 13:57:35,Surprised they don't have the BIG fences up around everything like they do Lafayette Park in anticipation of Jan 6th unrest.,2,0,0,surprised dont big fences like lafayette park anticipation jan 6th unrest,"[('Lafayette Park', 'FAC'), ('Jan 6th', 'DATE')]",0.05,"[101, 4527, 2123, 2102, 2502, 21549, 2066, 14425, 2380, 11162, 5553, 5351, 16591, 102]"
1346093526174625792,auntjody1976,1346093123353649153,wolfblitzer,2021-01-04 13:58:00,Let the count down begin,6,0,0,let count begin,[],-0.15555555555555559,"[101, 2292, 4175, 4088, 102]"
1346095350050934784,DocDavePerez,1346093123353649153,wolfblitzer,2021-01-04 14:05:15,I hope there is a bullet proof glass surrounding the President and VP.  Trump is creating outrage that will lead to violence.,5,0,1,hope bullet proof glass surrounding president vp trump creating outrage lead violence,"[('VP', 'ORG'), ('Trump', 'PERSON')]",0.0,"[101, 3246, 7960, 6947, 3221, 4193, 2343, 21210, 8398, 4526, 19006, 2599, 4808, 102]"
1346093898041593856,KathyCalder6,1346093123353649153,wolfblitzer,2021-01-04 13:59:29,"We are watching. We can't wait
 ",3,0,0,watching wait,[],0.0,"[101, 3666, 3524, 102]"
1346094233036460040,Dolpff,1346093123353649153,wolfblitzer,2021-01-04 14:00:49,"Trump will tell the world that he had 100,000’s and Biden hardly any (fully ignoring Covid) and by that he ‘won’ the elections. Same claim that his rallies had a higher turn out equals winning.",2,0,0,trump tell world 100000s biden hardly fully ignoring covid won elections claim rallies higher turn equals winning,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('100,000', 'CARDINAL'), ('Biden', 'PERSON'), ('Covid', 'PERSON')]",0.11458333333333333,"[101, 8398, 2425, 2088, 6694, 8889, 2015, 7226, 2368, 6684, 3929, 9217, 2522, 17258, 2180, 3864, 4366, 22867, 3020, 2735, 19635, 3045, 102]"
1346095070253084673,kevbateson,1346093123353649153,wolfblitzer,2021-01-04 14:04:08,Probably still be a larger crowd than the Giant Cheeto got...,2,0,0,probably larger crowd giant cheeto got,[],0.0,"[101, 2763, 3469, 4306, 5016, 18178, 18903, 2288, 102]"
1346108944725499904,sandybrowne7,1346093123353649153,wolfblitzer,2021-01-04 14:59:16,"Biden does not have an issue with crowd size, like someone else! He is more concerned about citizens keeping safe, unlike someone else.... just saying ",2,0,0,biden does issue crowd size like concerned citizens keeping safe unlike just saying,"[('Biden', 'ORG')]",0.5,"[101, 7226, 2368, 2515, 3277, 4306, 2946, 2066, 4986, 4480, 4363, 3647, 4406, 2074, 3038, 102]"
1346094500310118400,gapch1964,1346093123353649153,wolfblitzer,2021-01-04 14:01:52,Gotta see it! Thanks for sharing Wolf for the folks that can't attend.,1,0,0,gotta thanks sharing wolf folks attend,"[('Wolf', 'PERSON')]",0.2,"[101, 10657, 4283, 6631, 4702, 12455, 5463, 102]"
1346096972453842944,Luv2Fly737,1346093123353649153,wolfblitzer,2021-01-04 14:11:42,No the crowd will be limited because no one wants to see him. It's impossible for him to draw a crowd. And he will always be if he makes it an illegitimate President. Elected by fraudulent votes.,1,0,2,crowd limited wants impossible draw crowd makes illegitimate president elected fraudulent votes,[],-0.17936507936507937,"[101, 4306, 3132, 4122, 5263, 4009, 4306, 3084, 18102, 2343, 2700, 27105, 4494, 102]"
1346099754938339329,sawacapital,1346093123353649153,wolfblitzer,2021-01-04 14:22:45,"@YoushayRizvi
 your homie",1,0,0,youshayrizvi homie,[],0.0,"[101, 2017, 7377, 12541, 10993, 5737, 7570, 9856, 102]"
1346111763343765506,dhusker73,1346093123353649153,wolfblitzer,2021-01-04 15:10:28,Yes. Was our longest walk. It is a large bldg,1,0,0,yes longest walk large bldg,[],0.21428571428571427,"[101, 2748, 6493, 3328, 2312, 1038, 6392, 2290, 102]"
1346488949913636864,playmaker761900,1346093123353649153,wolfblitzer,2021-01-05 16:09:16,"Is their anyway to move up the Presidential inauguration? Trump is literally trying to kill our Democracy,  and the Republicans in Congress who know better are actually worse than he is. No one person can make a dent in this Democracy. Period!!!",1,0,0,presidential inauguration trump literally trying kill democracy republicans congress know better actually worse person make dent democracy period,"[('Republicans', 'NORP'), ('Congress', 'ORG')]",-0.140625,"[101, 4883, 17331, 8398, 6719, 2667, 3102, 7072, 10643, 3519, 2113, 2488, 2941, 4788, 2711, 2191, 21418, 7072, 2558, 102]"
1346093647574360068,1948_allan,1346093123353649153,wolfblitzer,2021-01-04 13:58:29,Finally Trump will be able to claim a bigger crowd..,0,0,0,finally trump able claim bigger crowd,[],0.16666666666666666,"[101, 2633, 8398, 2583, 4366, 7046, 4306, 102]"
1346093840621559808,KaMiSt72,1346093123353649153,wolfblitzer,2021-01-04 13:59:15,Please let them lock down entry to the town... Or better yet... Do the inauguration online and make a huge party later...,0,0,0,let lock entry town better inauguration online make huge party later,[],0.18611111111111112,"[101, 2292, 5843, 4443, 2237, 2488, 17331, 3784, 2191, 4121, 2283, 2101, 102]"

(Photo: An American flag waves in front of the Supreme Court building on Capitol Hill in Washington, D.C. via AP) #OANN",1400,139,41,good morning tune america news latest photo american flag waves supreme court building capitol hill washington dc ap oann,"[('morning', 'TIME'), ('One America News', 'ORG'), ('American', 'NORP'), ('the Supreme Court', 'ORG'), ('Capitol Hill', 'ORG'), ('Washington', 'GPE'), ('D.C.', 'GPE'), ('AP', 'ORG'), ('OANN', 'PERSON')]",0.5,"[101, 2204, 2851, 8694, 2637, 2739, 6745, 6302, 2137, 5210, 5975, 4259, 2457, 2311, 9424, 2940, 2899, 5887, 9706, 1051, 11639, 102]"
1336314342355197954,lorealcancer,1336314253318344704,OANN,2020-12-08 14:19:01,"And now, the end is near
As you face the final curtain
Your friends, They'll say it clear
They'll state your case of which I'm certain
You've lived a life of lies
You've grifted the conman's highway
But more, much more than this
Be on your MF’ing way
We did it our way",3,1,1,end near face final curtain friends theyll say clear theyll state case im certain youve lived life lies youve grifted conmans highway mfing way did way,"[('MF’ing', 'DATE')]",0.23571428571428568,"[101, 2203, 2379, 2227, 2345, 11002, 2814, 2027, 3363, 2360, 3154, 2027, 3363, 2110, 2553, 10047, 3056, 2017, 3726, 2973, 2166, 3658, 2017, 3726, 24665, 10128, 3064, 9530, 15154, 3307, 1049, 16294, 2290, 2126, 2106, 2126, 102]"
1336315084310630400,joe66872785,1336314253318344704,OANN,2020-12-08 14:21:58,Breaking News: Biden has won Georgia Again for the FOURTH TIme!!! ,2,0,0,breaking news biden won georgia fourth time,"[('Georgia Again', 'ORG')]",0.0,"[101, 4911, 2739, 7226, 2368, 2180, 4108, 2959, 2051, 102]"
1336322966062125062,fishersfolly,1336314253318344704,OANN,2020-12-08 14:53:17,Tune in for today's dose of lies hate and fear-mongering.,2,0,0,tune todays dose lies hate fearmongering,"[('today', 'DATE')]",-0.8,"[101, 8694, 2651, 2015, 13004, 3658, 5223, 3571, 8202, 4590, 2075, 102]"
1336324222163927042,jennybiz,1336314253318344704,OANN,2020-12-08 14:58:16,Praying for America! ,2,0,0,praying america,[],0.0,"[101, 14488, 2637, 102]"
1336314787622432770,4yearsNoTrophy,1336314253318344704,OANN,2020-12-08 14:20:47,Just a reminder that trump still lost the election ,1,0,0,just reminder trump lost election,[],0.0,"[101, 2074, 14764, 8398, 2439, 2602, 102]"
1336314407492739072,notinabluemoon,1336314253318344704,OANN,2020-12-08 14:19:16,How do I sign up?,0,0,0,sign,[],0.0,"[101, 3696, 102]"
1336314430448136197,Barbara67475620,1336314253318344704,OANN,2020-12-08 14:19:22,Will Alito's hearing be live streamed today?,0,0,1,alitos hearing live streamed today,"[(""Will Alito's"", 'PERSON'), ('today', 'DATE')]",0.13636363636363635,"[101, 4862, 13122, 4994, 2444, 18498, 2651, 102]"
1336314740415623168,NRio888,1336314253318344704,OANN,2020-12-08 14:20:36, should be bigger than that one,0,0,1,bigger,"[('one', 'CARDINAL')]",0.0,"[101, 7046, 102]"
1336317831642673153,PhillinaLewis,1336314253318344704,OANN,2020-12-08 14:32:53,"Thank you Texas!

https://scribd.com/document/487348469/TX-v-State-Motion-2020-12-07-FINAL…",0,0,0,thank texas,"[('Texas', 'GPE')]",0.0,"[101, 4067, 3146, 102]"
1336317903243776004,Roy71050782,1336314253318344704,OANN,2020-12-08 14:33:10,"Yet the scotus is avoiding their duty at this time, smh, the deep state is on all tiers!",0,0,0,scotus avoiding duty time smh deep state tiers,[],0.0,"[101, 8040, 4140, 2271, 9992, 4611, 2051, 15488, 2232, 2784, 2110, 7563, 2015, 102]"
1336323539255750656,willanna1,1336314253318344704,OANN,2020-12-08 14:55:34,May God Bless then No Guts for Justice No Glory for our Election Process!,0,0,0,god bless guts justice glory election process,[],0.0,"[101, 2643, 19994, 18453, 3425, 8294, 2602, 2832, 102]"
1336327739775700993,00Solid_Snake01,1336314253318344704,OANN,2020-12-08 15:12:15,Good morning US Supreme Court how are you going to help the people today by law & Justice,0,0,0,good morning supreme court going help people today law justice,"[('morning', 'TIME'), ('US Supreme Court', 'ORG'), ('today', 'DATE'), ('law & Justice', 'ORG')]",0.7,"[101, 2204, 2851, 4259, 2457, 2183, 2393, 2111, 2651, 2375, 3425, 102]"

(Photo: An American flag waves in front of the Supreme Court building on Capitol Hill in Washington, D.C. -- Patrick Semansky via AP) #OANN",1200,117,36,good morning tune america news latest photo american flag waves supreme court building capitol hill washington dc patrick semansky ap oann,"[('morning', 'TIME'), ('One America News', 'ORG'), ('American', 'NORP'), ('the Supreme Court', 'ORG'), ('Capitol Hill', 'ORG'), ('Washington', 'GPE'), ('D.C.', 'GPE'), ('Patrick Semansky', 'PERSON'), ('AP', 'ORG'), ('OANN', 'PERSON')]",0.5,"[101, 2204, 2851, 8694, 2637, 2739, 6745, 6302, 2137, 5210, 5975, 4259, 2457, 2311, 9424, 2940, 2899, 5887, 4754, 7367, 15154, 4801, 9706, 1051, 11639, 102]"
1334863962509357057,Bradicalxx86,1334862070706147328,OANN,2020-12-04 14:15:43,"I speak for all TRUE PATRIOTS when I say we need 
@realDonaldTrump
 to form a 3rd party and take the power from the CORRUPT Republicans. We NEED to take down REPULSUVE ROMNEY, Deep state AG Barr, and Terrible Toomey. #TrumpersForAmerica !!!",3,0,1,speak true patriots say need realdonaldtrump form 3rd party power corrupt republicans need repulsuve romney deep state ag barr terrible toomey trumpersforamerica,"[('@realDonaldTrump\n ', 'PERSON'), ('3rd', 'ORDINAL'), ('Republicans', 'NORP'), ('NEED', 'ORG'), ('Deep', 'NORP'), ('AG Barr', 'PERSON'), ('Terrible Toomey', 'ORG')]",-0.2175925925925926,"[101, 3713, 2995, 11579, 2360, 2342, 2613, 5280, 19058, 24456, 2361, 2433, 3822, 2283, 2373, 13593, 10643, 2342, 16360, 28426, 22909, 19615, 2784, 2110, 12943, 19820, 6659, 2205, 4168, 2100, 8398, 2545, 29278, 14074, 14735, 102]"
1334863293429780481,RichieSkaggs,1334862070706147328,OANN,2020-12-04 14:13:04,"Since Facebook REMOVED our group of 200k members, we have regrouped yet again. Find us on Facebook, ‘The ORIGINAL, We The People, have had enough’. To rejoin/join our FINE GROUP of REAL PATRIOTS ",1,0,1,facebook removed group 200k members regrouped facebook original people rejoinjoin fine group real patriots,"[('200k', 'ORG'), ('ORIGINAL', 'ORG'), ('FINE GROUP', 'ORG')]",0.24791666666666667,"[101, 9130, 3718, 2177, 3263, 2243, 2372, 19723, 22107, 2098, 9130, 2434, 2111, 25261, 5558, 2378, 2986, 2177, 2613, 11579, 102]"
1334870183664627714,abaa1642,1334862070706147328,OANN,2020-12-04 14:40:27,Tune in for the latest fake news.,1,0,0,tune latest fake news,[],0.0,"[101, 8694, 6745, 8275, 2739, 102]"
1334862210091241472,VChCng73055661,1334862070706147328,OANN,2020-12-04 14:08:46,Good morning,0,0,0,good morning,"[('morning', 'TIME')]",0.7,"[101, 2204, 2851, 102]"
1334862558281404421,WPssngr,1334862070706147328,OANN,2020-12-04 14:10:09,No thanks,0,0,0,thanks,[],-0.1,"[101, 4283, 102]"
1334862645787234304,BakeUGreatAgain,1334862070706147328,OANN,2020-12-04 14:10:29,"#BAKINGNEWS  the Senate has agreed these #Buttertarts are delicious! 
@Allrecipes
#BakeAmericaGreatAgain
1 ½ cups packed brown sugar 
2 eggs 
½ cup butter 
2 cups raisins (opt)
2 tbl heavy cream 
1 cup walnuts (opt)
30 (2”) unbaked tart shells",0,0,0,bakingnews senate agreed buttertarts delicious allrecipes bakeamericagreatagain 1 cups packed brown sugar 2 eggs cup butter 2 cups raisins opt 2 tbl heavy cream 1 cup walnuts opt 30 2 unbaked tart shells,"[('#', 'CARDINAL'), ('Senate', 'ORG'), ('Buttertarts', 'PERSON'), ('1', 'CARDINAL'), ('2', 'CARDINAL'), ('2', 'CARDINAL'), ('2', 'CARDINAL'), ('1 cup', 'QUANTITY'), ('30', 'CARDINAL'), ('2', 'CARDINAL')]",0.4,"[101, 21522, 2638, 9333, 4001, 3530, 12136, 7559, 3215, 12090, 2035, 2890, 6895, 10374, 8670, 3489, 14074, 14735, 17603, 6790, 23805, 2078, 1015, 10268, 8966, 2829, 5699, 1016, 6763, 2452, 12136, 1016, 10268, 15547, 11493, 2015, 23569, 1016, 26419, 2140, 3082, 6949, 1015, 2452, 18489, 2015, 23569, 2382, 1016, 4895, 3676, 8126, 16985, 2102, 10986, 102]"
1334862676657364995,brtnhll77,1334862070706147328,OANN,2020-12-04 14:10:37,https://salon.com/2020/12/03/trumps-outrageous-lies-used-to-be-terrifying--now-theyre-just-pathetic/…,0,0,0,,[],0.0,"[101, 102]"
1346165064865357824,DemMaj4Israel,1346165064865357824,None,2021-01-04 18:42:16,"Join DMFI & 
@cspan
 Communications Director 
@HowardMortman
 on Tuesday, January 12th as we view rare video clips of landmark moments in US-Israel relations on Capitol Hill & look at Howard Mortman's new book, ""When Rabbis Bless Congress.""

RSVP: https://us02web.zoom.us/webinar/register/1116076317477/WN_iT8-Y5yURRm00t7G8UejVg…",11,0,1,join dmfi cspan communications director howardmortman tuesday january 12th view rare video clips landmark moments usisrael relations capitol hill look howard mortmans new book rabbis bless congress rsvp,"[('Tuesday, January 12th', 'DATE'), ('US', 'GPE'), ('Israel', 'GPE'), ('Capitol Hill &', 'ORG'), (""Howard Mortman's"", 'PERSON'), ('Rabbis Bless Congress', 'ORG')]",0.21818181818181817,"[101, 3693, 1040, 2213, 8873, 20116, 9739, 4806, 2472, 4922, 5302, 5339, 2386, 9857, 2254, 5940, 3193, 4678, 2678, 15281, 8637, 5312, 2149, 2483, 16652, 2140, 4262, 9424, 2940, 2298, 4922, 22294, 15154, 2047, 2338, 25602, 19994, 3519, 12667, 2615, 2361, 102]"
1346200366837358593,chbooksdc,1346200366837358593,None,2021-01-04 21:02:33,"One of you probably knows a crazy Kennedy buff who may need this Bobby Kennedy inscribed first edition. $1,750 https://capitolhillbooks-dc.com/pages/books/8316/robert-f-kennedy/just-friends-and-brave-enemies-inscribed-and-signed-to-betty-and-frederick-vreeland…",32,2,3,probably knows crazy kennedy buff need bobby kennedy inscribed edition 1750,"[('One', 'CARDINAL'), ('Kennedy', 'PERSON'), ('Bobby Kennedy', 'PERSON'), ('1,750', 'MONEY')]",-0.175,"[101, 2763, 4282, 4689, 5817, 23176, 2342, 6173, 5817, 14551, 3179, 18171, 102]"
1346202110862512128,Cindecency,1346200366837358593,chbooksdc,2021-01-04 21:09:29,As someone who wore a Bobby Kennedy necklace until I lost it in 2015  2006-2015 me would have bankrupted myself to get this,2,0,1,wore bobby kennedy necklace lost 2015 20062015 bankrupted,"[('Bobby Kennedy', 'PERSON'), ('2015  2006-2015', 'DATE')]",0.0,"[101, 5078, 6173, 5817, 13016, 2439, 2325, 2294, 11387, 16068, 17482, 2098, 102]"
1346193966966988803,thehill,1346193966966988803,None,2021-01-04 20:37:07,DC mayor activates National Guard ahead of pro-Trump demonstrations http://hill.cm/bopjRfV,676,231,89,dc mayor activates national guard ahead protrump demonstrations,"[('National Guard', 'ORG')]",0.0,"[101, 5887, 3664, 20544, 2015, 2120, 3457, 3805, 4013, 24456, 2361, 13616, 102]"
1346227689695436806,locoashes,1346193966966988803,thehill,2021-01-04 22:51:07,This is wrong! DC doesn’t just belong to democrats!!!,1,0,0,wrong dc doesnt just belong democrats,"[('DC', 'GPE'), ('democrats', 'NORP')]",-1.0,"[101, 3308, 5887, 2987, 2102, 2074, 7141, 8037, 102]"
1346200866899046400,kcooptime,1346193966966988803,thehill,2021-01-04 21:04:32,"Wow. But mayors and govs rejected the assistance of the national guard while their cities were burned, rioter, and looted for months. Crazy.",20,3,2,wow mayors govs rejected assistance national guard cities burned rioter looted months crazy,"[('months', 'DATE')]",-0.25,"[101, 10166, 21941, 18079, 2015, 5837, 5375, 2120, 3457, 3655, 5296, 11421, 2121, 27775, 2706, 4689, 102]"
1346194524805210113,legalobserver1,1346193966966988803,thehill,2021-01-04 20:39:20,please give them the “clear the street for the church photoshoot” treatment,10,0,1,clear street church photoshoot treatment,[],0.10000000000000002,"[101, 3154, 2395, 2277, 7760, 23416, 3949, 102]"
1346195367558262785,DeniseB69150266,1346193966966988803,thehill,2021-01-04 20:42:41,...Because we conservatives are are peacefully protesting. What hypocrisy!!,9,0,3,conservatives peacefully protesting hypocrisy,[],0.390625,"[101, 11992, 21614, 21248, 1044, 22571, 10085, 6935, 2100, 102]"
1346194202770726914,Grey_Obelisk,1346193966966988803,thehill,2021-01-04 20:38:03,She should close the bars and restaurants.  Real hardship for a Trumper is coffee without vanilla creamer.,5,0,3,close bars restaurants real hardship trumper coffee vanilla creamer,"[('Trumper', 'ORG')]",0.2,"[101, 2485, 6963, 7884, 2613, 26479, 8398, 2121, 4157, 21161, 6949, 2121, 102]"
1346234987150979074,LaMaldadPR,1346193966966988803,thehill,2021-01-04 23:20:07,How convenient. She never activates it when Antifa destroys the city.,3,1,0,convenient activates antifa destroys city,"[('Antifa', 'PERSON')]",0.0,"[101, 14057, 20544, 2015, 3424, 7011, 20735, 2103, 102]"
1346194223888887809,Deplorablemoo,1346193966966988803,thehill,2021-01-04 20:38:08,I’m pretty sure it wasn’t Trump supporters that were smashing buildings and burning places down all summer long,2,1,1,im pretty sure wasnt trump supporters smashing buildings burning places summer long,[],0.1361111111111111,"[101, 10047, 3492, 2469, 2347, 2102, 8398, 6793, 21105, 3121, 5255, 3182, 2621, 2146, 102]"
1346212874612572163,djdec20,1346193966966988803,thehill,2021-01-04 21:52:15,But forgot they existed when the far left were burning down the city,2,1,0,forgot existed far left burning city,[],-0.018518518518518528,"[101, 9471, 5839, 2521, 2187, 5255, 2103, 102]"
1346201951575293952,realSaganRitual,1346193966966988803,thehill,2021-01-04 21:08:51,"They're activating 340 personnel!  Hear that, Proud Boys and other nutters? The National Guard hears your Million MAGA plans and estimates they can control the lot of you with a handful of real soldiers. I can't wait to see how proud you are when reality hits ",2,0,2,theyre activating 340 personnel hear proud boys nutters national guard hears million maga plans estimates control lot handful real soldiers wait proud reality hits,"[('340', 'CARDINAL'), ('Proud Boys', 'PERSON'), ('The National Guard', 'ORG'), ('Million', 'CARDINAL'), ('MAGA', 'ORG')]",0.41875,"[101, 2027, 2890, 2552, 17441, 16029, 5073, 2963, 7098, 3337, 17490, 7747, 2120, 3457, 14994, 2454, 23848, 2050, 3488, 10035, 2491, 2843, 9210, 2613, 3548, 3524, 7098, 4507, 4978, 102]"
1346206965287055361,MaryHol94769673,1346193966966988803,thehill,2021-01-04 21:28:46,"good
have them searched too as they did to us at the Obama inaugural...they should have  sections where everybody is checked and backpacks scanned

National Guard",2,0,0,good searched did obama inauguralthey sections everybody checked backpacks scanned national guard,"[('Obama', 'PERSON')]",0.7,"[101, 2204, 9022, 2106, 8112, 7725, 10760, 2100, 5433, 7955, 7039, 13383, 2015, 11728, 2120, 3457, 102]"
1345869806776545283,thehill,1345869806776545283,None,2021-01-03 23:09:01,JUST IN: Georgia Democratic lawmaker to seek censure of Trump over Georgia call http://hill.cm/aPtLDsi,463,98,29,just georgia democratic lawmaker seek censure trump georgia,"[('Georgia', 'GPE'), ('Democratic', 'NORP'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Georgia', 'GPE')]",0.0,"[101, 2074, 4108, 3537, 2375, 8571, 6148, 8292, 3619, 5397, 8398, 4108, 102]"
1345872422554066944,bloominglife12,1345869806776545283,thehill,2021-01-03 23:19:25,Jail would be more appropriate  how many times is he going to get away with his wannabe mob antics.,5,0,1,jail appropriate times going away wannabe mob antics,[],0.35,"[101, 7173, 6413, 2335, 2183, 2185, 10587, 4783, 11240, 27440, 102]"
1345870871563554816,jfcxxxx,1345869806776545283,thehill,2021-01-03 23:13:15,"Trump doesn't understand censure. 
It has to be more for him to even notice.",4,0,0,trump doesnt understand censure notice,"[('Trump', 'ORG')]",0.5,"[101, 8398, 2987, 2102, 3305, 8292, 3619, 5397, 5060, 102]"
1345870190035218436,surecantpickem,1345869806776545283,thehill,2021-01-03 23:10:33,At this point cant we just have the secret service arrest him for trying to counterfeit an election,3,0,1,point just secret service arrest trying counterfeit election,[],-0.225,"[101, 2391, 2074, 3595, 2326, 6545, 2667, 4675, 21156, 2602, 102]"
1345873626134884352,votingfordogs,1345869806776545283,thehill,2021-01-03 23:24:12,he has no idea what censure means..... that Georgia lawmaker has more spine than most of the GOP!  Bravo sir!,2,0,0,idea censure means georgia lawmaker spine gop bravo sir,"[('Georgia', 'GPE'), ('GOP', 'ORG'), ('Bravo', 'NORP')]",0.640625,"[101, 2801, 8292, 3619, 5397, 2965, 4108, 2375, 8571, 8560, 2175, 2361, 17562, 2909, 102]"
1345870053485535233,RetroGeoff,1345869806776545283,thehill,2021-01-03 23:10:00,January 20th... Tick tock...,1,0,1,january 20th tick tock,"[('January 20th', 'DATE'), ('Tick', 'PERSON')]",0.0,"[101, 2254, 3983, 16356, 2000, 3600, 102]"
1345870211300339714,SaveOurDemocr11,1345869806776545283,thehill,2021-01-03 23:10:38,"@realDonaldTrump
 leave now.",1,0,0,realdonaldtrump leave,"[('@realDonaldTrump\n ', 'PERSON')]",0.0,"[101, 2613, 5280, 19058, 24456, 2361, 2681, 102]"
1345871247306055681,Christina6886,1345869806776545283,thehill,2021-01-03 23:14:45,Dont want him to resign then pence could give him a pardon.,1,0,1,dont want resign pence pardon,[],0.0,"[101, 2123, 2102, 2215, 12897, 7279, 3401, 14933, 102]"
1346142330580070408,Jason58269269,1345869806776545283,thehill,2021-01-04 17:11:56,"I am thinking about calling the NFL Commisioner to find the Denver Broncos ""just one more touchdown"" so that they beat the Raiders. I might also call my old school district and ask them for a few more A's.",1,0,0,thinking calling nfl commisioner denver broncos just touchdown beat raiders old school district ask,"[('NFL', 'ORG'), ('the Denver Broncos', 'FAC'), ('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('Raiders', 'PRODUCT')]",0.22499999999999998,"[101, 3241, 4214, 5088, 4012, 15630, 3258, 2121, 7573, 14169, 2074, 7921, 3786, 10642, 2214, 2082, 2212, 3198, 102]"
1345874805019594755,IanMCohen,1345869806776545283,thehill,2021-01-03 23:28:53,How about an arrest warrant.,0,0,0,arrest warrant,[],-0.05,"[101, 6545, 10943, 102]"
1345877068144263170,_chasestarr,1345869806776545283,thehill,2021-01-03 23:37:52,https://youtu.be/IKiyAy9vjrk cheaters,0,0,0,cheaters,[],0.0,"[101, 21910, 2545, 102]"
1345879025516888064,redsteve50,1345869806776545283,thehill,2021-01-03 23:45:39,... the very few times Trump acts Presidential gets so much coverage - situations like the call to Georgia - people just shrug and say thats Trump - I’m not surprised,0,0,1,times trump acts presidential gets coverage situations like georgia people just shrug say thats trump im surprised,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Georgia', 'GPE')]",-0.03666666666666667,"[101, 2335, 8398, 4490, 4883, 4152, 6325, 8146, 2066, 4108, 2111, 2074, 13409, 2360, 2008, 2015, 8398, 10047, 4527, 102]"
1345887054018846721,EngelinaOlstho1,1345869806776545283,thehill,2021-01-04 00:17:33,Censure shemsure... He needs to be arrested!,0,0,0,censure shemsure needs arrested,[],0.0,"[101, 8292, 3619, 5397, 2016, 5244, 5397, 3791, 4727, 102]"
1345889081427898372,MyInfoMaryMart1,1345869806776545283,thehill,2021-01-04 00:25:37,I wonder what Pence & Rubio have to say about this one?,0,0,0,wonder pence rubio say,"[('Pence & Rubio', 'ORG')]",0.0,"[101, 4687, 7279, 3401, 14548, 3695, 2360, 102]"
1345893542875557888,Antonio72675353,1345869806776545283,thehill,2021-01-04 00:43:20,Who leaked the call?,0,0,0,leaked,[],0.0,"[101, 15748, 102]"
1345898472139067392,dblereflection,1345869806776545283,thehill,2021-01-04 01:02:55,"impeach him again, history needs to know what a POS this republican is",0,0,0,impeach history needs know pos republican,"[('republican', 'NORP')]",0.0,"[101, 17727, 5243, 2818, 2381, 3791, 2113, 13433, 2015, 3951, 102]"
1334305839037943809,politico,1334305839037943809,None,2020-12-03 01:17:56,"The U.S. Capitol Christmas Tree is now lit 

This year's tree is a 55-foot tall Engelmann spruce from Western Colorado and is decorated with handmade ornaments. The Capitol Christmas Tree has been a tradition since 1964.  AP, Getty",317,51,14,capitol christmas tree lit years tree 55foot tall engelmann spruce western colorado decorated handmade ornaments capitol christmas tree tradition 1964 ap getty,"[('U.S.', 'GPE'), ('Capitol Christmas Tree', 'ORG'), ('year', 'DATE'), ('55-foot', 'QUANTITY'), ('Engelmann', 'ORG'), ('Western Colorado', 'LOC'), ('The Capitol Christmas Tree', 'EVENT'), ('1964', 'DATE'), ('AP', 'ORG')]",0.0,"[101, 9424, 4234, 3392, 5507, 2086, 3392, 4583, 13064, 4206, 25540, 23830, 2078, 19893, 2530, 5169, 7429, 2192, 21565, 24005, 9424, 4234, 3392, 4535, 3546, 9706, 2131, 3723, 102]"
1334307529401262083,politico,1334305839037943809,politico,2020-12-03 01:24:39,"Nancy Pelosi presided over the tree lighting ceremony tonight. “We say a prayer for all who cannot celebrate with the comfort of their friends and families around them and for those who have lost their lives and livelihood this year,” she said.",298,48,21,nancy pelosi presided tree lighting ceremony tonight say prayer celebrate comfort friends families lost lives livelihood year said,"[('Nancy Pelosi', 'PERSON'), ('tonight', 'TIME'), ('this year', 'DATE')]",0.0,"[101, 7912, 21877, 10483, 2072, 15506, 3392, 7497, 5103, 3892, 2360, 7083, 8439, 7216, 2814, 2945, 2439, 3268, 24585, 2095, 2056, 102]"
1334306929687093250,GolfcartMozart,1334305839037943809,politico,2020-12-03 01:22:16,Always so much prettier than the WH tree.,1,0,0,prettier wh tree,"[('WH', 'ORG')]",0.2,"[101, 3653, 6916, 2121, 1059, 2232, 3392, 102]"
1334311274331697153,MrGrinch1234,1334305839037943809,politico,2020-12-03 01:39:32,"Who fucking cares. 264,000+ dead and rising. My god, the US is so damn broken ",1,0,0,fucking cares 264000 dead rising god damn broken,"[('264,000', 'CARDINAL'), ('US', 'GPE')]",-0.4000000000000001,"[101, 8239, 14977, 21611, 8889, 2692, 2757, 4803, 2643, 4365, 3714, 102]"
1334306597854654470,guyacampbell,1334305839037943809,politico,2020-12-03 01:20:57,I think the best way to photograph it is to cut off the bottom 60 feet so it just looks like a regular tree.,0,0,0,think best way photograph cut 60 feet just looks like regular tree,"[('60 feet', 'QUANTITY')]",0.5,"[101, 2228, 2190, 2126, 9982, 3013, 3438, 2519, 2074, 3504, 2066, 3180, 3392, 102]"
1334307070565371909,HumprheysGhost,1334305839037943809,politico,2020-12-03 01:22:50,Since 1964?,0,0,0,1964,"[('1964', 'DATE')]",0.0,"[101, 3546, 102]"
1334312914908483584,WynneJGriffith,1334305839037943809,politico,2020-12-03 01:46:03,Is that Nancy? Love it. ,0,0,0,nancy love,"[('Nancy', 'PERSON')]",0.5,"[101, 7912, 2293, 102]"
1334322514152083463,margaritasfor1,1334305839037943809,politico,2020-12-03 02:24:12,Bet that could have fed hundreds of families,0,0,0,bet fed hundreds families,"[('hundreds', 'CARDINAL')]",0.0,"[101, 6655, 7349, 5606, 2945, 102]"
1334307884054810638,RedRamLady1,1334305839037943809,politico,2020-12-03 01:26:04,Very pretty!,0,0,0,pretty,[],0.40625,"[101, 3492, 102]"
1346217601781927937,heatherhunterdc,1346217601781927937,None,2021-01-04 22:11:02,"From a Catholic Church on Capitol Hill... Masses will be ""locked"" during the protests on Wednesday.",0,2,1,catholic church capitol hill masses locked protests wednesday,"[('Capitol Hill', 'ORG'), ('Wednesday', 'DATE')]",0.0,"[101, 3234, 2277, 9424, 2940, 11678, 5299, 8090, 9317, 102]"
1340132257370169347,NEWSMAX,1340132257370169347,None,2020-12-19 03:10:03,'CHAZ is back': Barricade erected around Seattle Capitol Hill protest zone http://ow.ly/GBbp50CPkSt,581,258,203,chaz barricade erected seattle capitol hill protest zone,"[('Seattle', 'GPE'), ('Capitol Hill', 'ORG')]",0.0,"[101, 15775, 2480, 19820, 5555, 3207, 7019, 5862, 9424, 2940, 6186, 4224, 102]"
1340142227780227072,Mashburn4NC,1340132257370169347,NEWSMAX,2020-12-19 03:49:40,They do this because they are allowed to do it.  Nobody has the backbone to enforce law.,0,0,0,allowed backbone enforce law,[],0.0,"[101, 3039, 21505, 16306, 2375, 102]"
1340137076105293825,ShogunServicesX,1340132257370169347,NEWSMAX,2020-12-19 03:29:12,"A sequel!!

CHAZ 1 was very entertaining! I wonder if they're gonna bring the warlord back!

Maybe this time they'll get socialism and defunding police to work! Will they bring new characters in?

Will the fight scenes be better?

I'm getting my popcorn ",25,2,2,sequel chaz 1 entertaining wonder theyre gonna bring warlord maybe time theyll socialism defunding police work bring new characters fight scenes better im getting popcorn,"[('1', 'CARDINAL')]",0.36221590909090906,"[101, 8297, 15775, 2480, 1015, 14036, 4687, 2027, 2890, 6069, 3288, 16579, 2672, 2051, 2027, 3363, 14649, 13366, 8630, 2075, 2610, 2147, 3288, 2047, 3494, 2954, 5019, 2488, 10047, 2893, 24593, 102]"
1340133366121832449,Cackalacman,1340132257370169347,NEWSMAX,2020-12-19 03:14:27,"They should develop a chemical that they can add to water that smells like skunk piss and put it in the plane used for forrest fires, fly over this place and drop it. If they want to stay the whole place stinks. Worse than it already does.",18,0,4,develop chemical add water smells like skunk piss plane used forrest fires fly place drop want stay place stinks worse does,[],0.0,"[101, 4503, 5072, 5587, 2300, 14747, 2066, 15315, 16814, 18138, 4946, 2109, 16319, 8769, 4875, 2173, 4530, 2215, 2994, 2173, 27136, 2015, 4788, 2515, 102]"
1340132897420808192,VegasDavein,1340132257370169347,NEWSMAX,2020-12-19 03:12:35,Do these soy boys know they wouldn’t last 48 hours without the Police,17,0,0,soy boys know wouldnt 48 hours police,"[('last 48 hours', 'TIME')]",0.0,"[101, 25176, 3337, 2113, 2876, 2102, 4466, 2847, 2610, 102]"
1340133681982283777,JediWoods,1340132257370169347,NEWSMAX,2020-12-19 03:15:42,"Oh darn. No money for PD. Hopefully they funded Sanitation for all the stuff they destroy and trash. 

Summer of Love to Winter Wonderland is all... Right?",11,1,0,oh darn money pd hopefully funded sanitation stuff destroy trash summer love winter wonderland right,"[('Winter Wonderland', 'GPE')]",0.1952380952380952,"[101, 2821, 18243, 2078, 2769, 22851, 11504, 6787, 18723, 4933, 6033, 11669, 2621, 2293, 3467, 20365, 2157, 102]"
1340138805819363328,NachT666,1340132257370169347,NEWSMAX,2020-12-19 03:36:04,">Abolish the police.
>Nothing enforces to pay taxes.
>Supply lines are severed.
>Soy reserves dry up. 
>Welfare system collapses.
>Their trained enemies walk in, heavily armed, practically unopposed.

Just watch the spiraling regret.",13,0,0,abolish police enforces pay taxes supply lines severed soy reserves dry welfare collapses trained enemies walk heavily armed practically unopposed just watch spiraling regret,"[('Soy', 'PERSON')]",-0.13333333333333333,"[101, 11113, 20872, 2232, 2610, 16306, 2015, 3477, 7773, 4425, 3210, 16574, 25176, 8269, 4318, 7574, 25938, 4738, 6716, 3328, 4600, 4273, 8134, 17123, 2074, 3422, 12313, 2075, 9038, 102]"
1340146387694936064,CarolRedcrose,1340132257370169347,NEWSMAX,2020-12-19 04:06:12,As a resident of Washington state I find this frightening and I don’t understand why those in charge of this state don’t protect their citizens by putting a stop to the violence.,12,0,8,resident washington state frightening dont understand charge state dont protect citizens putting stop violence,"[('Washington', 'GPE')]",-0.5,"[101, 6319, 2899, 2110, 17115, 2123, 2102, 3305, 3715, 2110, 2123, 2102, 4047, 4480, 5128, 2644, 4808, 102]"
1340132856052416515,EJachno1,1340132257370169347,NEWSMAX,2020-12-19 03:12:26,Burning man Amateur dropouts with far left parents that could care less what their kids want or do in life. MOVE ALONG!,10,0,0,burning man amateur dropouts far left parents care kids want life,[],-0.08958333333333332,"[101, 5255, 2158, 5515, 4530, 12166, 2521, 2187, 3008, 2729, 4268, 2215, 2166, 102]"
1340135563169419266,JohannaAuterson,1340132257370169347,NEWSMAX,2020-12-19 03:23:11,When society has degraded to the point of celebrating this behavior the issues go far beyond that of political parties & presidential selections,10,2,1,society degraded point celebrating behavior issues far political parties presidential selections,[],0.05,"[101, 2554, 26131, 2391, 12964, 5248, 3314, 2521, 2576, 4243, 4883, 16310, 102]"
1340137604319199232,DublinMimi,1340132257370169347,NEWSMAX,2020-12-19 03:31:18,Can we work a deal to give Washington State and Oregon back to the British or something?,9,0,2,work deal washington state oregon british,"[('Washington State', 'GPE'), ('Oregon', 'GPE'), ('British', 'NORP')]",0.0,"[101, 2147, 3066, 2899, 2110, 5392, 2329, 102]"
1340133098877542406,LincolnMics,1340132257370169347,NEWSMAX,2020-12-19 03:13:23,"1/3rd pictured not wearing masks
9 of 9 pictured survived",8,0,0,13rd pictured wearing masks 9 9 pictured survived,"[('1/3rd', 'CARDINAL'), ('9', 'CARDINAL'), ('9', 'CARDINAL')]",0.0,"[101, 2410, 4103, 15885, 4147, 15806, 1023, 1023, 15885, 5175, 102]"
1340135940262678528,WebFeatWorks,1340132257370169347,NEWSMAX,2020-12-19 03:24:41,"This time around, how about we allow Seattle to destroy itself?",8,0,1,time allow seattle destroy,"[('Seattle', 'GPE')]",-0.2,"[101, 2051, 3499, 5862, 6033, 102]"
1340135890757271552,Christo70695005,1340132257370169347,NEWSMAX,2020-12-19 03:24:29,No FEDERAL BAIL OUT MONEY FOR THEIR FAILED CITY<,7,0,0,federal bail money failed city,[],-0.5,"[101, 2976, 15358, 2769, 3478, 2103, 102]"
1339650588339003393,thehill,1339650588339003393,None,2020-12-17 19:16:04,Atlantic City auctions off chance to blow up Trump Plaza http://hill.cm/nWWcKhB,207,65,32,atlantic city auctions chance blow trump plaza,"[('Atlantic City', 'GPE'), ('Trump Plaza', 'FAC')]",0.0,"[101, 4448, 2103, 10470, 2015, 3382, 6271, 8398, 8232, 102]"
1339650757352517632,SoloFlow786,1339650588339003393,thehill,2020-12-17 19:16:44,The NY AG has an implosion of Trump planned as well. See ya Jan 21st.,10,0,0,ny ag implosion trump planned ya jan 21st,"[('The NY AG', 'ORG'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('ya Jan 21st', 'DATE')]",0.0,"[101, 6396, 12943, 17727, 10483, 3258, 8398, 3740, 8038, 5553, 7398, 102]"
1339651160060403712,KevinJe49334546,1339650588339003393,thehill,2020-12-17 19:18:20,The man himself will implode as well. And good riddance.,3,0,0,man implode good riddance,[],0.7,"[101, 2158, 17727, 4135, 3207, 2204, 9436, 25514, 102]"
1339652161383358464,MM2LLC,1339650588339003393,thehill,2020-12-17 19:22:19,Jan 20th 2021 at 11:59AM would be an excellent detonation time and date.,3,0,0,jan 20th 2021 1159am excellent detonation time date,"[('Jan 20th', 'DATE')]",0.5,"[101, 5553, 3983, 25682, 10630, 2683, 3286, 6581, 20010, 7856, 3508, 2051, 3058, 102]"
1339652422122287104,patti_foss,1339650588339003393,thehill,2020-12-17 19:23:21,"Hoping it raises a lot for charity. Fitting since Trump and his family had to shut down their charity due to funds being used for personal and business related expenditures in NYC. No charity board for them again, before going to court mandatory classes to learn ethics.",3,0,0,hoping raises lot charity fitting trump family shut charity funds used personal business related expenditures nyc charity board going court mandatory classes learn ethics,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('NYC', 'LOC')]",0.04388888888888889,"[101, 5327, 13275, 2843, 5952, 11414, 8398, 2155, 3844, 5952, 5029, 2109, 3167, 2449, 3141, 22697, 16392, 5952, 2604, 2183, 2457, 10915, 4280, 4553, 9615, 102]"
1339651036248600577,stubbysquid,1339650588339003393,thehill,2020-12-17 19:17:51,@WaterDean,1,0,0,waterdean,"[('@WaterDean', 'NORP')]",0.0,"[101, 2300, 3207, 2319, 102]"
1339652190814670850,2hazy2c,1339650588339003393,thehill,2020-12-17 19:22:26,Is there no end to Don-the-Con's money making schemes?!!,1,0,1,end donthecons money making schemes,"[('Don', 'PERSON')]",0.0,"[101, 2203, 2123, 10760, 8663, 2015, 2769, 2437, 11683, 102]"
1339654962457030662,nik_eni,1339650588339003393,thehill,2020-12-17 19:33:27,"I'd take three steps back, spit on both hands, rub em together, do two spins, and slowly press the button.",1,0,0,id steps spit hands rub em spins slowly press button,"[('three', 'CARDINAL'), ('two', 'CARDINAL')]",-0.15000000000000002,"[101, 8909, 4084, 13183, 2398, 14548, 7861, 23371, 3254, 2811, 6462, 102]"
1339657169524957187,HeathyForLife,1339650588339003393,thehill,2020-12-17 19:42:13,....the clown show is coming to an end.,1,0,0,clown coming end,[],0.0,"[101, 15912, 2746, 2203, 102]"
1339662661588561921,Mjk1944K,1339650588339003393,thehill,2020-12-17 20:04:02,hilarious,1,0,0,hilarious,[],0.5,"[101, 26316, 102]"
1339672664252813314,Ahtrau,1339650588339003393,thehill,2020-12-17 20:43:47,Have they started the national lottery for who gets to put the boot to Trump's ass to get him out of the WH on January 20th?,1,0,0,started national lottery gets boot trumps ass wh january 20th,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('WH', 'ORG'), ('January 20th', 'DATE')]",0.0,"[101, 2318, 2120, 15213, 4152, 9573, 8398, 2015, 4632, 1059, 2232, 2254, 3983, 102]"
1339651933544587264,jean_bodon,1339650588339003393,thehill,2020-12-17 19:21:25,Like usual all your crazies love capitalism when it benefits you,0,0,0,like usual crazies love capitalism benefits,[],0.125,"[101, 2066, 5156, 13675, 16103, 2229, 2293, 16498, 6666, 102]"
1339652021608214528,GaryDR27,1339650588339003393,thehill,2020-12-17 19:21:46,"https://tenor.com/view/blow-up-nazi-symbol-be-gone-gif-15919880?utm_source=share-button&utm_medium=Social&utm_content=twitter… #BlowUp #NaziSymbol #BeGone via 
@gifkeyboard",0,0,0,blowup nazisymbol begone gifkeyboard,"[('#BlowUp #', 'MONEY'), ('NaziSymbol', 'PERSON')]",0.0,"[101, 6271, 6279, 13157, 24335, 14956, 11693, 5643, 21025, 24316, 3240, 6277, 102]"
1346221141208281092,thehill,1346221141208281092,None,2021-01-04 22:25:06,DC police chief wants to speak to new representative about plans to carry gun http://hill.cm/Sz3rY8K,132,48,29,dc police chief wants speak new representative plans carry gun,"[('DC', 'GPE')]",0.16818181818181818,"[101, 5887, 2610, 2708, 4122, 3713, 2047, 4387, 3488, 4287, 3282, 102]"
1346221722588966912,equalearthling,1346221141208281092,thehill,2021-01-04 22:27:24,I thought Republicans were the party of law and order?,8,0,1,thought republicans party law order,"[('Republicans', 'NORP')]",0.0,"[101, 2245, 10643, 2283, 2375, 2344, 102]"
1346222015934590976,MLMucci,1346221141208281092,thehill,2021-01-04 22:28:34,"""Keep your hands where I can see them"" is the first thing the DC police chief or any officer should say to Rep. 
@LaurenBoebert
 if she's illegally carrying her gun in Washington.",7,0,0,hands thing dc police chief officer say rep laurenboebert shes illegally carrying gun washington,"[('first', 'ORDINAL'), ('DC', 'GPE'), ('Washington', 'GPE')]",-0.125,"[101, 2398, 2518, 5887, 2610, 2708, 2961, 2360, 16360, 10294, 5092, 22669, 2102, 2016, 2015, 17800, 4755, 3282, 2899, 102]"
1346225257712115716,UmustBkiddingME,1346221141208281092,thehill,2021-01-04 22:41:27,"Pursuant to the United States and District of Columbia Criminal Codes, firearms, dangerous weapons, explosives, or incendiary devices are prohibited on U.S. Capitol Grounds. 

If she tries to carry a gun, they'll arrest her ass
#LawAndOrderParty",5,1,1,pursuant united states district columbia criminal codes firearms dangerous weapons explosives incendiary devices prohibited capitol grounds tries carry gun theyll arrest ass lawandorderparty,"[('the United States', 'GPE'), ('District of Columbia Criminal Codes', 'ORG'), ('U.S.', 'GPE'), ('LawAndOrderParty', 'MONEY')]",-0.28750000000000003,"[101, 27081, 2142, 2163, 2212, 3996, 4735, 9537, 13780, 4795, 4255, 14792, 4297, 10497, 17302, 5733, 10890, 9424, 5286, 5363, 4287, 3282, 2027, 3363, 6545, 4632, 2375, 28574, 26764, 19362, 3723, 102]"
1346222502301868035,LaBluedot,1346221141208281092,thehill,2021-01-04 22:30:30,Thank you DC Police Chief!,3,0,0,thank dc police chief,[],0.0,"[101, 4067, 5887, 2610, 2708, 102]"
1346222202358820865,AmyPond420_,1346221141208281092,thehill,2021-01-04 22:29:19,BoBert gonna cry if she can’t carry her safety blanket to work?! Wahhh cry snowflake!,1,0,1,bobert gonna carry safety blanket work wahhh snowflake,[],0.0,"[101, 3960, 8743, 6069, 4287, 3808, 8768, 2147, 22894, 23644, 4586, 10258, 13808, 102]"
1346225005332484102,karma_daydream,1346221141208281092,thehill,2021-01-04 22:40:27,http://realvail.com/the-many-contradictions-of-congressional-candidate-lauren-boebert/a9274/…,1,0,0,,[],0.0,"[101, 102]"
1346221561506881538,GodsWar72067826,1346221141208281092,thehill,2021-01-04 22:26:46,"They can talk, but the law is with the Reps",0,0,2,talk law reps,[],0.0,"[101, 2831, 2375, 16360, 2015, 102]"
1346221727748153345,aspfrt,1346221141208281092,thehill,2021-01-04 22:27:26,"Tyrannical Rule, DemocRats are sick.",0,0,0,tyrannical rule democrats sick,"[('DemocRats', 'NORP')]",-0.7142857142857143,"[101, 5939, 5521, 20913, 3627, 8037, 5305, 102]"
1346222377127075841,TheRealPest,1346221141208281092,thehill,2021-01-04 22:30:00,He should be more worried about gun crime in DC from the natives there.,0,0,1,worried gun crime dc natives,"[('DC', 'GPE')]",0.5,"[101, 5191, 3282, 4126, 5887, 12493, 102]"
1346222687786418177,pfrpeppermint,1346221141208281092,thehill,2021-01-04 22:31:15,"“I just want to find 11,780 votes.” In an hour long call with Secretary of State Raffensperger, trying to over turn the election. TRUMP BLACKMAILED RAFFENSPERGER if he didn’t change the results, he would not get re-elected,and go to jail. 
https://washingtonpost.com/politics/trump-raffensperger-call-georgia-vote/2021/01/03/d45acb92-4dc4-11eb-bda4-615aaefd0555_story.html…",0,0,0,just want 11780 votes hour long secretary state raffensperger trying turn election trump blackmailed raffensperger didnt change results reelectedand jail,"[('11,780', 'CARDINAL'), ('an hour', 'TIME'), ('State', 'ORG'), ('Raffensperger', 'PERSON'), ('TRUMP', 'ORG'), ('https://washingtonpost.com/politics/trump-raffensperger-call-georgia-vote/2021/01/03/d45acb92-4dc4-11eb-bda4-615aaefd0555_story.html', 'PERSON')]",-0.07500000000000001,"[101, 2074, 2215, 12567, 17914, 4494, 3178, 2146, 3187, 2110, 7148, 18940, 17668, 4590, 2667, 2735, 2602, 8398, 25044, 2098, 7148, 18940, 17668, 4590, 2134, 2102, 2689, 3463, 20847, 5685, 7173, 102]"
1346222986752360448,ColetteNester,1346221141208281092,thehill,2021-01-04 22:32:26,"Yeah, all we need in DC is another gun nutter......along with Trumps “proud boys” we have more than enough I think....",0,0,0,yeah need dc gun nutteralong trumps proud boys think,"[('DC', 'GPE'), ('Trumps', 'PERSON')]",0.43333333333333335,"[101, 3398, 2342, 5887, 3282, 17490, 14621, 10052, 8398, 2015, 7098, 3337, 2228, 102]"
1346224671692349441,beach_beer5269,1346221141208281092,thehill,2021-01-04 22:39:08,lol ... should obey the DC LAW ... u ,0,0,0,lol obey dc law u,[],0.8,"[101, 8840, 2140, 15470, 5887, 2375, 1057, 102]"
1346224894011273217,BumfuzzledXr,1346221141208281092,thehill,2021-01-04 22:40:01,So I guess it's okay to carry a weapon in the White House then?,0,0,0,guess okay carry weapon white house,"[('the White House', 'ORG')]",0.25,"[101, 3984, 3100, 4287, 5195, 2317, 2160, 102]"
1346224988559437827,r1chardeldridge,1346221141208281092,thehill,2021-01-04 22:40:23,"Members of Congress have the authority to declare war. Is someone saying they can't be trusted to carry a firearm? Furthermore, they are high profile people who make decisions that affect, for good or bad, the lives of billions of people. They should be armed.",0,0,0,members congress authority declare war saying trusted carry firearm furthermore high profile people make decisions affect good bad lives billions people armed,"[('Congress', 'ORG'), ('billions', 'CARDINAL')]",0.05333333333333338,"[101, 2372, 3519, 3691, 13520, 2162, 3038, 9480, 4287, 23646, 7297, 2152, 6337, 2111, 2191, 6567, 7461, 2204, 2919, 3268, 25501, 2111, 4273, 102]"
1346225347751268354,Lucianowrites,1346221141208281092,thehill,2021-01-04 22:41:49,"This is expressly illegal, incredibly so, and it is amazingly dangerous for her to try and do this. Jesus Fucking Christ.",0,0,0,expressly illegal incredibly amazingly dangerous try jesus fucking christ,"[('Jesus Fucking Christ', 'PERSON')]",-0.19999999999999998,"[101, 4671, 2135, 6206, 11757, 29350, 4795, 3046, 4441, 8239, 4828, 102]"
1346249110228111361,Byb2021,1346221141208281092,thehill,2021-01-05 00:16:14,Just another “loca”...,0,0,0,just loca,[],0.0,"[101, 2074, 8840, 3540, 102]"
1339763837856342017,thehill,1339763837856342017,None,2020-12-18 02:46:05,Atlantic City auctions off chance to blow up Trump Plaza http://hill.cm/iDyrWaf,162,38,17,atlantic city auctions chance blow trump plaza,"[('Atlantic City', 'GPE'), ('Trump Plaza http://hill.cm/iDyrWaf', 'FAC')]",0.0,"[101, 4448, 2103, 10470, 2015, 3382, 6271, 8398, 8232, 102]"
1339764086721003521,DavidHull50,1339763837856342017,thehill,2020-12-18 02:47:04,Will trump be in there?,6,0,1,trump,[],0.0,"[101, 8398, 102]"
1339765054309359617,fastballhitter1,1339763837856342017,thehill,2020-12-18 02:50:55,Shouldn’t need more than a bit of wind.,4,0,0,shouldnt need bit wind,[],0.5,"[101, 5807, 2102, 2342, 2978, 3612, 102]"
1339765354902540288,ErinReadsStuff,1339763837856342017,thehill,2020-12-18 02:52:06,"I will pay $800M. 

Unrelated: can anyone lend me $799.99M",3,0,0,pay 800m unrelated lend 79999m,"[('800M.', 'MONEY'), ('$799.99M', 'MONEY')]",0.0,"[101, 3477, 5385, 2213, 15142, 18496, 6535, 2683, 2683, 2683, 2213, 102]"
1339765845380255745,pans44,1339763837856342017,thehill,2020-12-18 02:54:03,Greatness,0,0,0,greatness,"[('Greatness', 'ORG')]",0.0,"[101, 2307, 2791, 102]"
1339766026582560768,mydogisgorgeous,1339763837856342017,thehill,2020-12-18 02:54:47,hahahhahahaha. What a phuqqing #moron Maybe HE should push the button ,0,0,0,hahahhahahaha phuqqing moron maybe push button,"[('moron', 'PERSON')]",-0.8,"[101, 5292, 3270, 23644, 23278, 3270, 3270, 6887, 2226, 4160, 19784, 22822, 2239, 2672, 5245, 6462, 102]"
1339769198839513088,OverboostedOne,1339763837856342017,thehill,2020-12-18 03:07:23,"So 
@realDonaldTrump
 makes the mistake of trying to revitalize the armpit of America and this is his thanks. Nice.

Atlantic City is DEAD and Trump isn't the only one who lost their shirt on that shithole.",0,0,0,realdonaldtrump makes mistake trying revitalize armpit america thanks nice atlantic city dead trump isnt lost shirt shithole,"[('@realDonaldTrump\n ', 'PERSON'), ('America', 'GPE'), ('Atlantic City', 'GPE'), ('DEAD', 'ORG'), ('Trump', 'ORG')]",0.15000000000000002,"[101, 2613, 5280, 19058, 24456, 2361, 3084, 6707, 2667, 7065, 18400, 4697, 2849, 23270, 2637, 4283, 3835, 4448, 2103, 2757, 8398, 3475, 2102, 2439, 3797, 4485, 11484, 102]"
1339775477892964353,WriterTrans,1339763837856342017,thehill,2020-12-18 03:32:20,If feels likre everything will refute be be hey,0,0,0,feels likre refute hey,"[('likre everything', 'PERSON')]",0.0,"[101, 5683, 5622, 21638, 2063, 25416, 10421, 4931, 102]"
1339764427738894336,obsceneporn,1339763837856342017,thehill,2020-12-18 02:48:25,This is doing incredible damage to our country and the presidency. Despicable and dangerous.,0,0,0,doing incredible damage country presidency despicable dangerous,[],0.15000000000000002,"[101, 2725, 9788, 4053, 2406, 8798, 4078, 24330, 3085, 4795, 102]"
1339764962345050114,FedUpPatriot717,1339763837856342017,thehill,2020-12-18 02:50:33,"Democrats are such sick, disgusting people.",0,0,0,democrats sick disgusting people,"[('Democrats', 'NORP')]",-0.5714285714285715,"[101, 8037, 5305, 19424, 2111, 102]"
1339766841762148352,sue52491494,1339763837856342017,thehill,2020-12-18 02:58:01,Where is Bill Gates!?,0,0,0,gates,"[('Bill Gates', 'PERSON')]",0.0,"[101, 6733, 102]"
1339807873757540352,thehill,1339807873757540352,None,2020-12-18 05:41:04,Atlantic City auctions off chance to blow up Trump Plaza http://hill.cm/VV7OfDX,169,42,17,atlantic city auctions chance blow trump plaza,"[('Atlantic City', 'GPE'), ('Trump Plaza', 'FAC')]",0.0,"[101, 4448, 2103, 10470, 2015, 3382, 6271, 8398, 8232, 102]"
1339808597958565888,ScottysParadigm,1339807873757540352,thehill,2020-12-18 05:43:56,How much to do NY tRump tower too? (Kidding) ,2,0,0,ny trump tower kidding,"[('NY', 'GPE')]",0.2,"[101, 6396, 8398, 3578, 12489, 102]"
1339808107388661761,cam_03w,1339807873757540352,thehill,2020-12-18 05:41:59,Can I start the bid at $1 that’s how much all trump property is worth ,1,0,1,start bid 1 thats trump property worth,"[('1', 'MONEY')]",0.25,"[101, 2707, 7226, 1015, 2008, 2015, 8398, 3200, 4276, 102]"
1339809093704364033,FabFreddy4,1339807873757540352,thehill,2020-12-18 05:45:55,".
@realDonaldTrump
 another failure of yours. Man it never ends well with you.",1,0,0,realdonaldtrump failure man ends,"[('@realDonaldTrump\n ', 'PERSON')]",-0.3166666666666667,"[101, 2613, 5280, 19058, 24456, 2361, 4945, 2158, 4515, 102]"
1339811030264737793,orangeblutattoo,1339807873757540352,thehill,2020-12-18 05:53:36,"Which reminds me, Trump opened the Taj Mahal casino in 1990, and roughly a year later it went bankrupt.  How the hell do you do that?",1,0,1,reminds trump opened taj mahal casino 1990 roughly year later went bankrupt hell,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Taj Mahal', 'ORG'), ('1990', 'DATE'), ('roughly a year later', 'DATE')]",-0.05,"[101, 15537, 8398, 2441, 11937, 3501, 27913, 9270, 2901, 5560, 2095, 2101, 2253, 17482, 3109, 102]"
1339808415435120640,DaMidKidDB1,1339807873757540352,thehill,2020-12-18 05:43:13,pay me what he owes and I'll pay attention,0,0,1,pay owes ill pay attention,[],0.0,"[101, 3477, 24381, 5665, 3477, 3086, 102]"
1339808991166275585,pookeypies7,1339807873757540352,thehill,2020-12-18 05:45:30,Wuttt? Posting this?,0,0,0,wuttt posting,[],0.0,"[101, 8814, 4779, 2102, 14739, 102]"
1339812248408252418,jenoakley81,1339807873757540352,thehill,2020-12-18 05:58:27,The one time I don’t have extra cash ,0,0,0,time dont extra cash,"[('one', 'CARDINAL')]",0.0,"[101, 2051, 2123, 2102, 4469, 5356, 102]"
1339826302489145344,heels_my,1339807873757540352,thehill,2020-12-18 06:54:17,"This, the mark of a 'successful' business man... he's full of shit and his failed, abandoned properties are landmarks of his immense failures.",0,0,0,mark successful business man hes shit failed abandoned properties landmarks immense failures,[],0.08000000000000003,"[101, 2928, 3144, 2449, 2158, 2002, 2015, 4485, 3478, 4704, 5144, 16209, 14269, 15428, 102]"
1339811006328025089,CasieKay8,1339807873757540352,thehill,2020-12-18 05:53:31,Democrats are riddled with mental illness.,0,0,0,democrats riddled mental illness,"[('Democrats', 'NORP')]",-0.1,"[101, 8037, 21834, 2094, 5177, 7355, 102]"
1339815177508823040,TreatTod,1339807873757540352,thehill,2020-12-18 06:10:05,What’s great is he’s still a billionaire and you’re all a bunch of losers and you’re poor,0,0,0,whats great hes billionaire youre bunch losers youre poor,[],0.0666666666666667,"[101, 2054, 2015, 2307, 2002, 2015, 22301, 2115, 2063, 9129, 23160, 2115, 2063, 3532, 102]"
1339987827581444096,TreatTod,1339807873757540352,thehill,2020-12-18 17:36:08,Always remember Trump is a billionaire president that gets to screw a supermodel every night you you’re a keyboard warrior a failure and you have absolutely nothing and no money,0,0,0,remember trump billionaire president gets screw supermodel night youre keyboard warrior failure absolutely money,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('every night', 'TIME')]",-0.05833333333333335,"[101, 3342, 8398, 22301, 2343, 4152, 11224, 3565, 5302, 9247, 2305, 2115, 2063, 9019, 6750, 4945, 7078, 2769, 102]"
1342477473292890112,thehill,1342477473292890112,None,2020-12-25 14:29:06,"Anger at Trump and lawmakers mounts among governors: ""I’ve never been so disgusted with Congress"" http://hill.cm/8gvguEG",182,39,26,anger trump lawmakers mounts governors ive disgusted congress,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Congress', 'ORG')]",-0.85,"[101, 4963, 8398, 2375, 12088, 19363, 11141, 4921, 2063, 17733, 3519, 102]"
1342477900868685826,Grey_Obelisk,1342477473292890112,thehill,2020-12-25 14:30:48,Stop saying Congress.  The fault is 100% Republicans in Congress.,16,0,0,stop saying congress fault 100 republicans congress,"[('Congress', 'ORG'), ('100%', 'PERCENT'), ('Republicans', 'NORP'), ('Congress', 'ORG')]",0.0,"[101, 2644, 3038, 3519, 6346, 2531, 10643, 3519, 102]"
1342477979910332416,DietrichAdonis,1342477473292890112,thehill,2020-12-25 14:31:07,If Governors are disgusted...think of the millions of Americans who were counting on that #StimulusPackage,10,0,0,governors disgustedthink millions americans counting stimuluspackage,"[('Governors', 'PERSON'), ('millions', 'CARDINAL'), ('Americans', 'NORP'), ('StimulusPackage', 'ORG')]",0.0,"[101, 11141, 17733, 15222, 8950, 8817, 4841, 10320, 19220, 23947, 4270, 102]"
1342481017005895680,MPFIED,1342477473292890112,thehill,2020-12-25 14:43:11,It's Trump and Republicans in Congress. Be specific when you are directing your ire.,8,0,0,trump republicans congress specific directing ire,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('Republicans', 'NORP'), ('Congress', 'ORG')]",0.0,"[101, 8398, 10643, 3519, 3563, 9855, 20868, 2063, 102]"
1342480631385776128,gerilarkin,1342477473292890112,thehill,2020-12-25 14:41:39,"There's nothing you can do. They don't care about the people. They are evil men playing chess with Americans lives, while getting richer.",2,1,0,theres dont care people evil men playing chess americans lives getting richer,"[('Americans', 'NORP')]",-1.0,"[101, 2045, 2015, 2123, 2102, 2729, 2111, 4763, 2273, 2652, 7433, 4841, 3268, 2893, 26108, 102]"
1342482602507325443,DavisLilian,1342477473292890112,thehill,2020-12-25 14:49:29,We are all disgusted..,2,0,0,disgusted,[],-1.0,"[101, 17733, 102]"
1342482727287848961,NaplesGreta,1342477473292890112,thehill,2020-12-25 14:49:58,AMAZING- interviewees requested anonymity so as not to anger Trump or republicans in Congress......,2,0,0,amazing interviewees requested anonymity anger trump republicans congress,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('republicans', 'NORP'), ('Congress', 'ORG')]",-0.04999999999999993,"[101, 6429, 4357, 10285, 7303, 2019, 16585, 16383, 4963, 8398, 10643, 3519, 102]"
1342494036771434497,lesliekaren,1342477473292890112,thehill,2020-12-25 15:34:55,"“The chief of staff, ... asked for anonymity to avoid angering both Trump and Senate Republicans, who said they won’t consider new aid to state & local governments”

Why is everybody so afraid of 45? What am I missing? He IS just a man, right?  Crazy, but still just a man. ",1,0,0,chief staff asked anonymity avoid angering trump senate republicans said wont consider new aid state local governments everybody afraid 45 missing just man right crazy just man,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Senate', 'ORG'), ('Republicans', 'NORP'), ('45', 'CARDINAL')]",-0.16298701298701299,"[101, 2708, 3095, 2356, 2019, 16585, 16383, 4468, 4963, 2075, 8398, 4001, 10643, 2056, 2180, 2102, 5136, 2047, 4681, 2110, 2334, 6867, 7955, 4452, 3429, 4394, 2074, 2158, 2157, 4689, 2074, 2158, 102]"
1342504533918887939,GlasstetterMark,1342477473292890112,thehill,2020-12-25 16:16:38,At least the Democrats were ready with $2000.,1,0,1,democrats ready 2000,"[('Democrats', 'NORP'), ('2000', 'MONEY')]",-0.04999999999999999,"[101, 8037, 3201, 2456, 102]"
1342511365202829315,aprlegalview,1342477473292890112,thehill,2020-12-25 16:43:46,They need to specifiy. They should be angry at Trump and Republican lawmakers.,1,0,0,need specifiy angry trump republican lawmakers,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Republican', 'NORP')]",-0.5,"[101, 2342, 28699, 10128, 28008, 4854, 8398, 3951, 2375, 12088, 102]"
1342556989830918145,thehill,1342556989830918145,None,2020-12-25 19:45:04,"Anger at Trump and lawmakers mounts among governors: ""I’ve never been so disgusted with Congress"" http://hill.cm/F1UNtB5",155,39,31,anger trump lawmakers mounts governors ive disgusted congress,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Congress', 'ORG')]",-0.85,"[101, 4963, 8398, 2375, 12088, 19363, 11141, 4921, 2063, 17733, 3519, 102]"
1342558475960918017,Therealbp65,1342556989830918145,thehill,2020-12-25 19:50:58,I’ve never been so angry at governors and mayors.  This is all THEIR fault from the get-go!,11,0,0,ive angry governors mayors fault getgo,[],-0.625,"[101, 4921, 2063, 4854, 11141, 21941, 6346, 2131, 3995, 102]"
1342561283959386112,AMcCorm77526975,1342556989830918145,thehill,2020-12-25 20:02:08,"Don’t they mean 
@SenateGOP
 instead of “Congress”?
@HouseDemocrats
 @SpeakerPelosi
 had the HEROS BILL which included $1200 individual stimulus, $600 Unemployment Insurance add-on AND funds for State/Local Govts.
passed and sent the Senate in MAY where @senatemajldr SAT ON IT.",5,1,1,dont mean senategop instead congress housedemocrats speakerpelosi heros included 1200 individual stimulus 600 unemployment insurance addon funds statelocal govts passed sent senate senatemajldr sat,"[('Congress', 'ORG'), ('@HouseDemocrats\n @SpeakerPelosi\n ', 'MONEY'), ('HEROS', 'ORG'), ('1200', 'MONEY'), ('600', 'MONEY'), ('State/Local Govts', 'ORG'), ('Senate', 'ORG'), ('MAY', 'DATE')]",-0.15625,"[101, 2123, 2102, 2812, 4001, 3995, 2361, 2612, 3519, 7431, 6633, 10085, 8609, 2015, 5882, 11880, 20049, 5394, 2015, 2443, 14840, 3265, 19220, 5174, 12163, 5427, 5587, 2239, 5029, 2110, 4135, 9289, 22410, 2015, 2979, 2741, 4001, 4001, 2863, 3501, 6392, 2099, 2938, 102]"
1342558865309708290,sandhillshrink,1342556989830918145,thehill,2020-12-25 19:52:31,Should have been. McConnell and his band of fascists have been operating for decades.,3,0,0,mcconnell band fascists operating decades,"[('McConnell', 'PERSON'), ('decades', 'DATE')]",0.0,"[101, 28514, 2316, 14870, 2015, 4082, 5109, 102]"
1342562647066099712,TheUnitedWhirld,1342556989830918145,thehill,2020-12-25 20:07:33,"When you say ""the federal government had not made a single step"" don't you mean the GOP?",3,0,0,say federal government single step dont mean gop,"[('GOP', 'ORG')]",-0.1919642857142857,"[101, 2360, 2976, 2231, 2309, 3357, 2123, 2102, 2812, 2175, 2361, 102]"
1342557077223469060,shanetweetsall,1342556989830918145,thehill,2020-12-25 19:45:25,We all feel the same,1,0,0,feel,[],0.0,"[101, 2514, 102]"
1342559183481294855,linderje,1342556989830918145,thehill,2020-12-25 19:53:47,"""The federal government has not made a single step of the process of dealing with this pandemic easier. Not one single step.” So ... getting you PPE and masks and ventilators and hospital ships mean nothing? You are looking for cash so you can keep everyone locked down. SORRY!",1,0,1,federal government single step process dealing pandemic easier single step getting ppe masks ventilators hospital ships mean looking cash locked sorry,"[('one', 'CARDINAL'), ('PPE', 'ORG')]",-0.2471825396825397,"[101, 2976, 2231, 2309, 3357, 2832, 7149, 6090, 3207, 7712, 6082, 2309, 3357, 2893, 4903, 2063, 15806, 18834, 11733, 6591, 2902, 3719, 2812, 2559, 5356, 5299, 3374, 102]"
1342568595759493120,Nett0yan7,1342556989830918145,thehill,2020-12-25 20:31:11,"When a con man who has destroyed everything he has ever touched, is elected president of the US, WTF DID THEY EXPECT?",1,0,0,man destroyed touched elected president wtf did expect,"[('US', 'GPE')]",-0.5,"[101, 2158, 3908, 5028, 2700, 2343, 1059, 24475, 2106, 5987, 102]"
1342557309885706247,duarteddf,1342556989830918145,thehill,2020-12-25 19:46:20,25/12/2020 | MEGA CULTO GLOBAL DE NATAL COM OS PROFETAS DO SENHOR | #GloriousChristmasService,0,0,0,25122020 mega culto global natal com os profetas senhor gloriouschristmasservice,"[('25/12/2020', 'CARDINAL'), ('CULTO GLOBAL DE NATAL COM OS', 'ORG')]",0.0,"[101, 22582, 19317, 2692, 11387, 13164, 8754, 2080, 3795, 17489, 4012, 9808, 11268, 12928, 2015, 12411, 16368, 14013, 26654, 9335, 8043, 7903, 2063, 102]"
1342559907342675968,psbono21,1342556989830918145,thehill,2020-12-25 19:56:40,"USA has never been so embarrassed , ashamed , disgusted w/ a potus .",0,0,0,usa embarrassed ashamed disgusted w potus,"[('USA', 'GPE')]",-1.0,"[101, 3915, 10339, 14984, 17733, 1059, 8962, 2271, 102]"
1342560207281512449,JohnWDawkins,1342556989830918145,thehill,2020-12-25 19:57:51,Pathetic Loser.,0,0,0,pathetic loser,"[('Pathetic Loser', 'ORG')]",-1.0,"[101, 17203, 10916, 102]"
1346141862562828290,thehill,1346141862562828290,None,2021-01-04 17:10:04,Georgia Democratic lawmaker to seek censure of Trump over Georgia call http://hill.cm/mlhS2Ff,151,40,19,georgia democratic lawmaker seek censure trump georgia,"[('Georgia', 'GPE'), ('Democratic', 'NORP'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Georgia', 'GPE')]",0.0,"[101, 4108, 3537, 2375, 8571, 6148, 8292, 3619, 5397, 8398, 4108, 102]"
1346142176686735360,PaulPanusorn,1346141862562828290,thehill,2021-01-04 17:11:19,Trump committed felony election tampering!,0,0,0,trump committed felony election tampering,[],0.0,"[101, 8398, 5462, 24648, 2602, 17214, 4842, 2075, 102]"
1346142261491367936,cuidaddy,1346141862562828290,thehill,2021-01-04 17:11:39,We need to ban political parties. Adams and Jefferson messed everything up.,0,0,0,need ban political parties adams jefferson messed,"[('Jefferson', 'PERSON')]",0.0,"[101, 2342, 7221, 2576, 4243, 5922, 7625, 18358, 102]"
1346143032429727744,IMrankov,1346141862562828290,thehill,2021-01-04 17:14:43,"Unfortunately, he will get away with it! Like everything else!! Despite your ""totemic constitution"" you keep swearing by every time!! Rich people in America don't go to jail!! Law is for the poor!!",0,0,0,unfortunately away like despite totemic constitution swearing time rich people america dont jail law poor,"[('America', 'GPE'), ('Law', 'PERSON')]",-0.3515625,"[101, 6854, 2185, 2066, 2750, 2000, 18532, 2594, 4552, 25082, 2051, 4138, 2111, 2637, 2123, 2102, 7173, 2375, 3532, 102]"
1346143902517100550,eutrophy121,1346141862562828290,thehill,2021-01-04 17:18:11,Trump is working overtime on his cynicism signaling.,0,0,0,trump working overtime cynicism signaling,"[('Trump', 'ORG')]",0.0,"[101, 8398, 2551, 12253, 22330, 8713, 2964, 14828, 102]"
1346923468282068992,brittaread,1346141862562828290,thehill,2021-01-06 20:55:54,Trump is guilty of treason.,0,0,0,trump guilty treason,"[('Trump', 'ORG')]",-0.5,"[101, 8398, 5905, 14712, 102]"
1346151079868846080,Bbee1960,1346141862562828290,thehill,2021-01-04 17:46:42,Censure is not enough,0,0,0,censure,[],0.0,"[101, 8292, 3619, 5397, 102]"
1346142537749204998,chuck79394571,1346141862562828290,thehill,2021-01-04 17:12:45,"And the USA is supposed to be the anchor of democracy around the world, Trump will create another Vietnam, this time happening in the USA where trump will promote his own form of communism using the military against civilians of the states that will not support him as a dictator",0,0,0,usa supposed anchor democracy world trump create vietnam time happening usa trump promote form communism using military civilians states support dictator,"[('USA', 'GPE'), ('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Vietnam', 'GPE'), ('USA', 'GPE')]",0.25,"[101, 3915, 4011, 8133, 7072, 2088, 8398, 3443, 5148, 2051, 6230, 3915, 8398, 5326, 2433, 15523, 2478, 2510, 9272, 2163, 2490, 21237, 102]"
1346146199926165506,_Serene_96,1346141862562828290,thehill,2021-01-04 17:27:18,"A Georgian censure; An attempt of censoring the attempt of receiving the relevant facts on the table regarding the election. An attempt of bandwagoning in favor of the popular media narrative which entails dismissing all election insecurity claims, resulting in sheepish applause.",0,0,0,georgian censure attempt censoring attempt receiving relevant facts table regarding election attempt bandwagoning favor popular media narrative entails dismissing election insecurity claims resulting sheepish applause,"[('Georgian', 'NORP')]",0.5,"[101, 9166, 8292, 3619, 5397, 3535, 8292, 29577, 2075, 3535, 4909, 7882, 8866, 2795, 4953, 2602, 3535, 2316, 4213, 7446, 2075, 5684, 2759, 2865, 7984, 4372, 22081, 28913, 2602, 16021, 8586, 25137, 4447, 4525, 8351, 4509, 20737, 102]"
1344688181644566528,thehill,1344688181644566528,None,2020-12-31 16:53:40,"President Trump departs West Palm Beach, Florida, for a flight to Washington, D.C.",138,58,93,president trump departs west palm beach florida flight washington dc,"[('Trump', 'PERSON'), ('West Palm Beach', 'GPE'), ('Florida', 'GPE'), ('Washington', 'GPE'), ('D.C.', 'GPE')]",0.0,"[101, 2343, 8398, 18280, 2015, 2225, 5340, 3509, 3516, 3462, 2899, 5887, 102]"
1344688723343020032,victorycharliev,1344688181644566528,thehill,2020-12-31 16:55:49,Crowd is almost as big as his inauguration in 2016,8,1,1,crowd big inauguration 2016,"[('2016', 'DATE')]",0.0,"[101, 4306, 2502, 17331, 2355, 102]"
1344689083486851073,findingsuccess2,1344688181644566528,thehill,2020-12-31 16:57:15,"Maybe not all the people in N. Korea are forced to praise their leader, some might be like these guys",6,0,2,maybe people n korea forced praise leader like guys,"[('N. Korea', 'GPE')]",-0.30000000000000004,"[101, 2672, 2111, 1050, 4420, 3140, 8489, 3003, 2066, 4364, 102]"
1344689797374255104,RonKeating5,1344688181644566528,thehill,2020-12-31 17:00:05,Look... never seen so many uneducated together since Trumps rallies...,2,1,0,look seen uneducated trumps rallies,"[('Trumps', 'PERSON')]",0.5,"[101, 2298, 2464, 16655, 8566, 12921, 8398, 2015, 22867, 102]"
1344690024906895361,rebekahkfreitas,1344688181644566528,thehill,2020-12-31 17:00:59,Awww. Look at his 20 supporters.,3,0,0,awww look 20 supporters,"[('Awww', 'PERSON'), ('20', 'CARDINAL')]",0.0,"[101, 22091, 2860, 2860, 2298, 2322, 6793, 102]"
1344688667961348096,strayhorsedad,1344688181644566528,thehill,2020-12-31 16:55:36,Why is he going back to DC?,2,0,5,going dc,"[('DC', 'GPE')]",0.0,"[101, 2183, 5887, 102]"
1344688775272800257,jerrycannon5,1344688181644566528,thehill,2020-12-31 16:56:01,It's a cult.,2,0,0,cult,[],0.0,"[101, 8754, 102]"
1344705229309292544,PublicPerson4,1344688181644566528,thehill,2020-12-31 18:01:24,Trump is going back to Washington to continue his coup plans. I hope police are ready for this ridiculous quest to overthrow the government. Every in congress & house that rises against the electoral vote counting should be recognized as traitors & expelled.,2,0,0,trump going washington continue coup plans hope police ready ridiculous quest overthrow government congress house rises electoral vote counting recognized traitors expelled,"[('Trump', 'ORG'), ('Washington', 'GPE'), ('congress & house', 'ORG')]",-0.04444444444444443,"[101, 8398, 2183, 2899, 3613, 8648, 3488, 3246, 2610, 3201, 9951, 8795, 16857, 2231, 3519, 2160, 9466, 6092, 3789, 10320, 3858, 17328, 2015, 10016, 102]"
1344688801260646401,ScottLaday,1344688181644566528,thehill,2020-12-31 16:56:07,How much they pay them?,1,0,0,pay,[],0.2,"[101, 3477, 102]"
